var zn=Object.defineProperty;var Gn=(e,t,a)=>t in e?zn(e,t,{enumerable:!0,configurable:!0,writable:!0,value:a}):e[t]=a;var B=(e,t,a)=>(Gn(e,typeof t!="symbol"?t+"":t,a),a);import{r as Y,R as Xe,t as Qn}from"./index-3e528c0f.js";function p(e){for(var t=arguments.length,a=new Array(t>1?t-1:0),n=1;n<t;n++)a[n-1]=arguments[n];throw new Error(typeof e=="number"?"[MobX] minified error nr: "+e+(a.length?" "+a.map(String).join(","):"")+". Find the full error at: https://github.com/mobxjs/mobx/blob/main/packages/mobx/src/errors.ts":"[MobX] "+e)}var Xn={};function ht(){return typeof globalThis<"u"?globalThis:typeof window<"u"?window:typeof global<"u"?global:typeof self<"u"?self:Xn}var Yt=Object.assign,Ee=Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptor,q=Object.defineProperty,Ue=Object.prototype,rt=[];Object.freeze(rt);var Ut={};Object.freeze(Ut);var Zn=typeof Proxy<"u",ea=Object.toString();function Ht(){Zn||p("Proxy not available")}function Ft(e){var t=!1;return function(){if(!t)return t=!0,e.apply(this,arguments)}}var Z=function(){};function O(e){return typeof e=="function"}function $(e){var t=typeof e;switch(t){case"string":case"symbol":case"number":return!0}return!1}function He(e){return e!==null&&typeof e=="object"}function I(e){if(!He(e))return!1;var t=Object.getPrototypeOf(e);if(t==null)return!0;var a=Object.hasOwnProperty.call(t,"constructor")&&t.constructor;return typeof a=="function"&&a.toString()===ea}function $t(e){var t=e==null?void 0:e.constructor;return t?t.name==="GeneratorFunction"||t.displayName==="GeneratorFunction":!1}function we(e,t,a){q(e,t,{enumerable:!1,writable:!0,configurable:!0,value:a})}function Kt(e,t,a){q(e,t,{enumerable:!1,writable:!1,configurable:!0,value:a})}function K(e,t){var a="isMobX"+e;return t.prototype[a]=!0,function(n){return He(n)&&n[a]===!0}}function ce(e){return e instanceof Map}function ye(e){return e instanceof Set}var zt=typeof Object.getOwnPropertySymbols<"u";function ta(e){var t=Object.keys(e);if(!zt)return t;var a=Object.getOwnPropertySymbols(e);return a.length?[].concat(t,a.filter(function(n){return Ue.propertyIsEnumerable.call(e,n)})):t}var ne=typeof Reflect<"u"&&Reflect.ownKeys?Reflect.ownKeys:zt?function(e){return Object.getOwnPropertyNames(e).concat(Object.getOwnPropertySymbols(e))}:Object.getOwnPropertyNames;function Gt(e){return e===null?null:typeof e=="object"?""+e:e}function N(e,t){return Ue.hasOwnProperty.call(e,t)}var na=Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptors||function(t){var a={};return ne(t).forEach(function(n){a[n]=Ee(t,n)}),a};function Tt(e,t){for(var a=0;a<t.length;a++){var n=t[a];n.enumerable=n.enumerable||!1,n.configurable=!0,"value"in n&&(n.writable=!0),Object.defineProperty(e,oa(n.key),n)}}function pt(e,t,a){return t&&Tt(e.prototype,t),a&&Tt(e,a),Object.defineProperty(e,"prototype",{writable:!1}),e}function ae(){return ae=Object.assign?Object.assign.bind():function(e){for(var t=1;t<arguments.length;t++){var a=arguments[t];for(var n in a)Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(a,n)&&(e[n]=a[n])}return e},ae.apply(this,arguments)}function Qt(e,t){e.prototype=Object.create(t.prototype),e.prototype.constructor=e,ot(e,t)}function ot(e,t){return ot=Object.setPrototypeOf?Object.setPrototypeOf.bind():function(n,r){return n.__proto__=r,n},ot(e,t)}function Ze(e){if(e===void 0)throw new ReferenceError("this hasn't been initialised - super() hasn't been called");return e}function aa(e,t){if(e){if(typeof e=="string")return Rt(e,t);var a=Object.prototype.toString.call(e).slice(8,-1);if(a==="Object"&&e.constructor&&(a=e.constructor.name),a==="Map"||a==="Set")return Array.from(e);if(a==="Arguments"||/^(?:Ui|I)nt(?:8|16|32)(?:Clamped)?Array$/.test(a))return Rt(e,t)}}function Rt(e,t){(t==null||t>e.length)&&(t=e.length);for(var a=0,n=new Array(t);a<t;a++)n[a]=e[a];return n}function ee(e,t){var a=typeof Symbol<"u"&&e[Symbol.iterator]||e["@@iterator"];if(a)return(a=a.call(e)).next.bind(a);if(Array.isArray(e)||(a=aa(e))||t&&e&&typeof e.length=="number"){a&&(e=a);var n=0;return function(){return n>=e.length?{done:!0}:{done:!1,value:e[n++]}}}throw new TypeError(`Invalid attempt to iterate non-iterable instance.
In order to be iterable, non-array objects must have a [Symbol.iterator]() method.`)}function ra(e,t){if(typeof e!="object"||e===null)return e;var a=e[Symbol.toPrimitive];if(a!==void 0){var n=a.call(e,t||"default");if(typeof n!="object")return n;throw new TypeError("@@toPrimitive must return a primitive value.")}return(t==="string"?String:Number)(e)}function oa(e){var t=ra(e,"string");return typeof t=="symbol"?t:String(t)}var j=Symbol("mobx-stored-annotations");function x(e){function t(a,n){be(a,n,e)}return Object.assign(t,e)}function be(e,t,a){N(e,j)||we(e,j,ae({},e[j])),pa(a)||(e[j][t]=a)}function ia(e){return N(e,j)||we(e,j,ae({},e[j])),e[j]}var l=Symbol("mobx administration"),Ae=function(){function e(a){a===void 0&&(a="Atom"),this.name_=void 0,this.isPendingUnobservation_=!1,this.isBeingObserved_=!1,this.observers_=new Set,this.batchId_=void 0,this.diffValue_=0,this.lastAccessedBy_=0,this.lowestObserverState_=h.NOT_TRACKING_,this.onBOL=void 0,this.onBUOL=void 0,this.name_=a,this.batchId_=u.inBatch?u.batchId:NaN}var t=e.prototype;return t.onBO=function(){this.onBOL&&this.onBOL.forEach(function(n){return n()})},t.onBUO=function(){this.onBUOL&&this.onBUOL.forEach(function(n){return n()})},t.reportObserved=function(){return yn(this)},t.reportChanged=function(){(!u.inBatch||this.batchId_!==u.batchId)&&(u.stateVersion=u.stateVersion<Number.MAX_SAFE_INTEGER?u.stateVersion+1:Number.MIN_SAFE_INTEGER,this.batchId_=NaN),k(),bn(this),S()},t.toString=function(){return this.name_},e}(),mt=K("Atom",Ae);function Xt(e,t,a){t===void 0&&(t=Z),a===void 0&&(a=Z);var n=new Ae(e);return t!==Z&&hr(n,t),a!==Z&&On(n,a),n}function sa(e,t){return e===t}function ca(e,t){return kt(e,t)}function ua(e,t){return kt(e,t,1)}function da(e,t){return Object.is?Object.is(e,t):e===t?e!==0||1/e===1/t:e!==e&&t!==t}var De={identity:sa,structural:ca,default:da,shallow:ua};function re(e,t,a){return xn(e)?e:Array.isArray(e)?g.array(e,{name:a}):I(e)?g.object(e,void 0,{name:a}):ce(e)?g.map(e,{name:a}):ye(e)?g.set(e,{name:a}):typeof e=="function"&&!bt(e)&&!We(e)?$t(e)?me(e):pe(a,e):e}function fa(e,t,a){if(e==null||ve(e)||Ge(e)||G(e)||ue(e))return e;if(Array.isArray(e))return g.array(e,{name:a,deep:!1});if(I(e))return g.object(e,void 0,{name:a,deep:!1});if(ce(e))return g.map(e,{name:a,deep:!1});if(ye(e))return g.set(e,{name:a,deep:!1})}function Fe(e){return e}function la(e,t){return kt(e,t)?t:e}var ha="override";function pa(e){return e.annotationType_===ha}function _e(e,t){return{annotationType_:e,options_:t,make_:ma,extend_:va}}function ma(e,t,a,n){var r;if((r=this.options_)!=null&&r.bound)return this.extend_(e,t,a,!1)===null?0:1;if(n===e.target_)return this.extend_(e,t,a,!1)===null?0:2;if(bt(a.value))return 1;var o=Zt(e,this,t,a,!1);return q(n,t,o),2}function va(e,t,a,n){var r=Zt(e,this,t,a);return e.defineProperty_(t,r,n)}function ga(e,t,a,n){t.annotationType_,n.value}function Zt(e,t,a,n,r){var o,i,s,c,d,f,m;r===void 0&&(r=u.safeDescriptors),ga(e,t,a,n);var v=n.value;if((o=t.options_)!=null&&o.bound){var D;v=v.bind((D=e.proxy_)!=null?D:e.target_)}return{value:oe((i=(s=t.options_)==null?void 0:s.name)!=null?i:a.toString(),v,(c=(d=t.options_)==null?void 0:d.autoAction)!=null?c:!1,(f=t.options_)!=null&&f.bound?(m=e.proxy_)!=null?m:e.target_:void 0),configurable:r?e.isPlainObject_:!0,enumerable:!1,writable:!r}}function en(e,t){return{annotationType_:e,options_:t,make_:wa,extend_:ya}}function wa(e,t,a,n){var r;if(n===e.target_)return this.extend_(e,t,a,!1)===null?0:2;if((r=this.options_)!=null&&r.bound&&(!N(e.target_,t)||!We(e.target_[t]))&&this.extend_(e,t,a,!1)===null)return 0;if(We(a.value))return 1;var o=tn(e,this,t,a,!1,!1);return q(n,t,o),2}function ya(e,t,a,n){var r,o=tn(e,this,t,a,(r=this.options_)==null?void 0:r.bound);return e.defineProperty_(t,o,n)}function ba(e,t,a,n){t.annotationType_,n.value}function tn(e,t,a,n,r,o){o===void 0&&(o=u.safeDescriptors),ba(e,t,a,n);var i=n.value;if(We(i)||(i=me(i)),r){var s;i=i.bind((s=e.proxy_)!=null?s:e.target_),i.isMobXFlow=!0}return{value:i,configurable:o?e.isPlainObject_:!0,enumerable:!1,writable:!o}}function vt(e,t){return{annotationType_:e,options_:t,make_:Aa,extend_:_a}}function Aa(e,t,a){return this.extend_(e,t,a,!1)===null?0:1}function _a(e,t,a,n){return ka(e,this,t,a),e.defineComputedProperty_(t,ae({},this.options_,{get:a.get,set:a.set}),n)}function ka(e,t,a,n){t.annotationType_,n.get}function $e(e,t){return{annotationType_:e,options_:t,make_:Sa,extend_:Ta}}function Sa(e,t,a){return this.extend_(e,t,a,!1)===null?0:1}function Ta(e,t,a,n){var r,o;return Ra(e,this),e.defineObservableProperty_(t,a.value,(r=(o=this.options_)==null?void 0:o.enhancer)!=null?r:re,n)}function Ra(e,t,a,n){t.annotationType_}var Oa="true",Ma=nn();function nn(e){return{annotationType_:Oa,options_:e,make_:Ja,extend_:ja}}function Ja(e,t,a,n){var r,o;if(a.get)return Ke.make_(e,t,a,n);if(a.set){var i=oe(t.toString(),a.set);return n===e.target_?e.defineProperty_(t,{configurable:u.safeDescriptors?e.isPlainObject_:!0,set:i})===null?0:2:(q(n,t,{configurable:!0,set:i}),2)}if(n!==e.target_&&typeof a.value=="function"){var s;if($t(a.value)){var c,d=(c=this.options_)!=null&&c.autoBind?me.bound:me;return d.make_(e,t,a,n)}var f=(s=this.options_)!=null&&s.autoBind?pe.bound:pe;return f.make_(e,t,a,n)}var m=((r=this.options_)==null?void 0:r.deep)===!1?g.ref:g;if(typeof a.value=="function"&&(o=this.options_)!=null&&o.autoBind){var v;a.value=a.value.bind((v=e.proxy_)!=null?v:e.target_)}return m.make_(e,t,a,n)}function ja(e,t,a,n){var r,o;if(a.get)return Ke.extend_(e,t,a,n);if(a.set)return e.defineProperty_(t,{configurable:u.safeDescriptors?e.isPlainObject_:!0,set:oe(t.toString(),a.set)},n);if(typeof a.value=="function"&&(r=this.options_)!=null&&r.autoBind){var i;a.value=a.value.bind((i=e.proxy_)!=null?i:e.target_)}var s=((o=this.options_)==null?void 0:o.deep)===!1?g.ref:g;return s.extend_(e,t,a,n)}var qa="observable",xa="observable.ref",Ea="observable.shallow",Da="observable.struct",an={deep:!0,name:void 0,defaultDecorator:void 0,proxy:!0};Object.freeze(an);function Oe(e){return e||an}var rn=$e(qa),Ba=$e(xa,{enhancer:Fe}),Pa=$e(Ea,{enhancer:fa}),Na=$e(Da,{enhancer:la}),on=x(rn);function Me(e){return e.deep===!0?re:e.deep===!1?Fe:Ia(e.defaultDecorator)}function Ca(e){var t;return e?(t=e.defaultDecorator)!=null?t:nn(e):void 0}function Ia(e){var t,a;return e&&(t=(a=e.options_)==null?void 0:a.enhancer)!=null?t:re}function sn(e,t,a){if($(t)){be(e,t,rn);return}return xn(e)?e:I(e)?g.object(e,t,a):Array.isArray(e)?g.array(e,t):ce(e)?g.map(e,t):ye(e)?g.set(e,t):typeof e=="object"&&e!==null?e:g.box(e,t)}Yt(sn,on);var Wa={box:function(t,a){var n=Oe(a);return new te(t,Me(n),n.name,!0,n.equals)},array:function(t,a){var n=Oe(a);return(u.useProxies===!1||n.proxy===!1?Cr:Mr)(t,Me(n),n.name)},map:function(t,a){var n=Oe(a);return new Pn(t,Me(n),n.name)},set:function(t,a){var n=Oe(a);return new In(t,Me(n),n.name)},object:function(t,a,n){return H(function(){return Jn(u.useProxies===!1||(n==null?void 0:n.proxy)===!1?Te({},n):kr({},n),t,a)})},ref:x(Ba),shallow:x(Pa),deep:on,struct:x(Na)},g=Yt(sn,Wa),cn="computed",La="computed.struct",un=vt(cn),Va=vt(La,{equals:De.structural}),Ke=function(t,a){if($(a))return be(t,a,un);if(I(t))return x(vt(cn,t));var n=I(a)?a:{};return n.get=t,n.name||(n.name=t.name||""),new he(n)};Object.assign(Ke,un);Ke.struct=x(Va);var Ot,Mt,Be=0,Ya=1,Ua=(Ot=(Mt=Ee(function(){},"name"))==null?void 0:Mt.configurable)!=null?Ot:!1,Jt={value:"action",configurable:!0,writable:!1,enumerable:!1};function oe(e,t,a,n){a===void 0&&(a=!1);function r(){return Ha(e,a,t,n||this,arguments)}return r.isMobxAction=!0,Ua&&(Jt.value=e,q(r,"name",Jt)),r}function Ha(e,t,a,n,r){var o=Fa(e,t);try{return a.apply(n,r)}catch(i){throw o.error_=i,i}finally{$a(o)}}function Fa(e,t,a,n){var r=!1,o=0,i=u.trackingDerivation,s=!t||!i;k();var c=u.allowStateChanges;s&&(z(),c=gt(!0));var d=yt(!0),f={runAsAction_:s,prevDerivation_:i,prevAllowStateChanges_:c,prevAllowStateReads_:d,notifySpy_:r,startTime_:o,actionId_:Ya++,parentActionId_:Be};return Be=f.actionId_,f}function $a(e){Be!==e.actionId_&&p(30),Be=e.parentActionId_,e.error_!==void 0&&(u.suppressReactionErrors=!0),wt(e.prevAllowStateChanges_),fe(e.prevAllowStateReads_),S(),e.runAsAction_&&C(e.prevDerivation_),u.suppressReactionErrors=!1}function gt(e){var t=u.allowStateChanges;return u.allowStateChanges=e,t}function wt(e){u.allowStateChanges=e}var dn;dn=Symbol.toPrimitive;var te=function(e){Qt(t,e);function t(n,r,o,i,s){var c;return o===void 0&&(o="ObservableValue"),s===void 0&&(s=De.default),c=e.call(this,o)||this,c.enhancer=void 0,c.name_=void 0,c.equals=void 0,c.hasUnreportedChange_=!1,c.interceptors_=void 0,c.changeListeners_=void 0,c.value_=void 0,c.dehancer=void 0,c.enhancer=r,c.name_=o,c.equals=s,c.value_=r(n,void 0,o),c}var a=t.prototype;return a.dehanceValue=function(r){return this.dehancer!==void 0?this.dehancer(r):r},a.set=function(r){this.value_,r=this.prepareNewValue_(r),r!==u.UNCHANGED&&this.setNewValue_(r)},a.prepareNewValue_=function(r){if(A(this)){var o=_(this,{object:this,type:E,newValue:r});if(!o)return u.UNCHANGED;r=o.newValue}return r=this.enhancer(r,this.value_,this.name_),this.equals(this.value_,r)?u.UNCHANGED:r},a.setNewValue_=function(r){var o=this.value_;this.value_=r,this.reportChanged(),T(this)&&R(this,{type:E,object:this,newValue:r,oldValue:o})},a.get=function(){return this.reportObserved(),this.dehanceValue(this.value_)},a.intercept_=function(r){return ke(this,r)},a.observe_=function(r,o){return o&&r({observableKind:"value",debugObjectName:this.name_,object:this,type:E,newValue:this.value_,oldValue:void 0}),Se(this,r)},a.raw=function(){return this.value_},a.toJSON=function(){return this.get()},a.toString=function(){return this.name_+"["+this.value_+"]"},a.valueOf=function(){return Gt(this.get())},a[dn]=function(){return this.valueOf()},t}(Ae),fn;fn=Symbol.toPrimitive;var he=function(){function e(a){this.dependenciesState_=h.NOT_TRACKING_,this.observing_=[],this.newObserving_=null,this.isBeingObserved_=!1,this.isPendingUnobservation_=!1,this.observers_=new Set,this.diffValue_=0,this.runId_=0,this.lastAccessedBy_=0,this.lowestObserverState_=h.UP_TO_DATE_,this.unboundDepsCount_=0,this.value_=new Ne(null),this.name_=void 0,this.triggeredBy_=void 0,this.isComputing_=!1,this.isRunningSetter_=!1,this.derivation=void 0,this.setter_=void 0,this.isTracing_=Pe.NONE,this.scope_=void 0,this.equals_=void 0,this.requiresReaction_=void 0,this.keepAlive_=void 0,this.onBOL=void 0,this.onBUOL=void 0,a.get||p(31),this.derivation=a.get,this.name_=a.name||"ComputedValue",a.set&&(this.setter_=oe("ComputedValue-setter",a.set)),this.equals_=a.equals||(a.compareStructural||a.struct?De.structural:De.default),this.scope_=a.context,this.requiresReaction_=a.requiresReaction,this.keepAlive_=!!a.keepAlive}var t=e.prototype;return t.onBecomeStale_=function(){Xa(this)},t.onBO=function(){this.onBOL&&this.onBOL.forEach(function(n){return n()})},t.onBUO=function(){this.onBUOL&&this.onBUOL.forEach(function(n){return n()})},t.get=function(){if(this.isComputing_&&p(32,this.name_,this.derivation),u.inBatch===0&&this.observers_.size===0&&!this.keepAlive_)it(this)&&(this.warnAboutUntrackedRead_(),k(),this.value_=this.computeValue_(!1),S());else if(yn(this),it(this)){var n=u.trackingContext;this.keepAlive_&&!n&&(u.trackingContext=this),this.trackAndCompute()&&Qa(this),u.trackingContext=n}var r=this.value_;if(je(r))throw r.cause;return r},t.set=function(n){if(this.setter_){this.isRunningSetter_&&p(33,this.name_),this.isRunningSetter_=!0;try{this.setter_.call(this.scope_,n)}finally{this.isRunningSetter_=!1}}else p(34,this.name_)},t.trackAndCompute=function(){var n=this.value_,r=this.dependenciesState_===h.NOT_TRACKING_,o=this.computeValue_(!0),i=r||je(n)||je(o)||!this.equals_(n,o);return i&&(this.value_=o),i},t.computeValue_=function(n){this.isComputing_=!0;var r=gt(!1),o;if(n)o=ln(this,this.derivation,this.scope_);else if(u.disableErrorBoundaries===!0)o=this.derivation.call(this.scope_);else try{o=this.derivation.call(this.scope_)}catch(i){o=new Ne(i)}return wt(r),this.isComputing_=!1,o},t.suspend_=function(){this.keepAlive_||(st(this),this.value_=void 0)},t.observe_=function(n,r){var o=this,i=!0,s=void 0;return cr(function(){var c=o.get();if(!i||r){var d=z();n({observableKind:"computed",debugObjectName:o.name_,type:E,object:o,newValue:c,oldValue:s}),C(d)}i=!1,s=c})},t.warnAboutUntrackedRead_=function(){},t.toString=function(){return this.name_+"["+this.derivation.toString()+"]"},t.valueOf=function(){return Gt(this.get())},t[fn]=function(){return this.valueOf()},e}(),ze=K("ComputedValue",he),h;(function(e){e[e.NOT_TRACKING_=-1]="NOT_TRACKING_",e[e.UP_TO_DATE_=0]="UP_TO_DATE_",e[e.POSSIBLY_STALE_=1]="POSSIBLY_STALE_",e[e.STALE_=2]="STALE_"})(h||(h={}));var Pe;(function(e){e[e.NONE=0]="NONE",e[e.LOG=1]="LOG",e[e.BREAK=2]="BREAK"})(Pe||(Pe={}));var Ne=function(t){this.cause=void 0,this.cause=t};function je(e){return e instanceof Ne}function it(e){switch(e.dependenciesState_){case h.UP_TO_DATE_:return!1;case h.NOT_TRACKING_:case h.STALE_:return!0;case h.POSSIBLY_STALE_:{for(var t=yt(!0),a=z(),n=e.observing_,r=n.length,o=0;o<r;o++){var i=n[o];if(ze(i)){if(u.disableErrorBoundaries)i.get();else try{i.get()}catch{return C(a),fe(t),!0}if(e.dependenciesState_===h.STALE_)return C(a),fe(t),!0}}return pn(e),C(a),fe(t),!1}}}function ln(e,t,a){var n=yt(!0);pn(e),e.newObserving_=new Array(e.observing_.length+100),e.unboundDepsCount_=0,e.runId_=++u.runId;var r=u.trackingDerivation;u.trackingDerivation=e,u.inBatch++;var o;if(u.disableErrorBoundaries===!0)o=t.call(a);else try{o=t.call(a)}catch(i){o=new Ne(i)}return u.inBatch--,u.trackingDerivation=r,Ka(e),fe(n),o}function Ka(e){for(var t=e.observing_,a=e.observing_=e.newObserving_,n=h.UP_TO_DATE_,r=0,o=e.unboundDepsCount_,i=0;i<o;i++){var s=a[i];s.diffValue_===0&&(s.diffValue_=1,r!==i&&(a[r]=s),r++),s.dependenciesState_>n&&(n=s.dependenciesState_)}for(a.length=r,e.newObserving_=null,o=t.length;o--;){var c=t[o];c.diffValue_===0&&gn(c,e),c.diffValue_=0}for(;r--;){var d=a[r];d.diffValue_===1&&(d.diffValue_=0,Ga(d,e))}n!==h.UP_TO_DATE_&&(e.dependenciesState_=n,e.onBecomeStale_())}function st(e){var t=e.observing_;e.observing_=[];for(var a=t.length;a--;)gn(t[a],e);e.dependenciesState_=h.NOT_TRACKING_}function hn(e){var t=z();try{return e()}finally{C(t)}}function z(){var e=u.trackingDerivation;return u.trackingDerivation=null,e}function C(e){u.trackingDerivation=e}function yt(e){var t=u.allowStateReads;return u.allowStateReads=e,t}function fe(e){u.allowStateReads=e}function pn(e){if(e.dependenciesState_!==h.UP_TO_DATE_){e.dependenciesState_=h.UP_TO_DATE_;for(var t=e.observing_,a=t.length;a--;)t[a].lowestObserverState_=h.UP_TO_DATE_}}var qe=function(){this.version=6,this.UNCHANGED={},this.trackingDerivation=null,this.trackingContext=null,this.runId=0,this.mobxGuid=0,this.inBatch=0,this.batchId=Number.MIN_SAFE_INTEGER,this.pendingUnobservations=[],this.pendingReactions=[],this.isRunningReactions=!1,this.allowStateChanges=!1,this.allowStateReads=!0,this.enforceActions=!0,this.spyListeners=[],this.globalReactionErrorHandlers=[],this.computedRequiresReaction=!1,this.reactionRequiresObservable=!1,this.observableRequiresReaction=!1,this.disableErrorBoundaries=!1,this.suppressReactionErrors=!1,this.useProxies=!0,this.verifyProxies=!1,this.safeDescriptors=!0,this.stateVersion=Number.MIN_SAFE_INTEGER},xe=!0,mn=!1,u=function(){var e=ht();return e.__mobxInstanceCount>0&&!e.__mobxGlobals&&(xe=!1),e.__mobxGlobals&&e.__mobxGlobals.version!==new qe().version&&(xe=!1),xe?e.__mobxGlobals?(e.__mobxInstanceCount+=1,e.__mobxGlobals.UNCHANGED||(e.__mobxGlobals.UNCHANGED={}),e.__mobxGlobals):(e.__mobxInstanceCount=1,e.__mobxGlobals=new qe):(setTimeout(function(){mn||p(35)},1),new qe)}();function za(){if((u.pendingReactions.length||u.inBatch||u.isRunningReactions)&&p(36),mn=!0,xe){var e=ht();--e.__mobxInstanceCount===0&&(e.__mobxGlobals=void 0),u=new qe}}function vn(){return u}function Ga(e,t){e.observers_.add(t),e.lowestObserverState_>t.dependenciesState_&&(e.lowestObserverState_=t.dependenciesState_)}function gn(e,t){e.observers_.delete(t),e.observers_.size===0&&wn(e)}function wn(e){e.isPendingUnobservation_===!1&&(e.isPendingUnobservation_=!0,u.pendingUnobservations.push(e))}function k(){u.inBatch===0&&(u.batchId=u.batchId<Number.MAX_SAFE_INTEGER?u.batchId+1:Number.MIN_SAFE_INTEGER),u.inBatch++}function S(){if(--u.inBatch===0){An();for(var e=u.pendingUnobservations,t=0;t<e.length;t++){var a=e[t];a.isPendingUnobservation_=!1,a.observers_.size===0&&(a.isBeingObserved_&&(a.isBeingObserved_=!1,a.onBUO()),a instanceof he&&a.suspend_())}u.pendingUnobservations=[]}}function yn(e){var t=u.trackingDerivation;return t!==null?(t.runId_!==e.lastAccessedBy_&&(e.lastAccessedBy_=t.runId_,t.newObserving_[t.unboundDepsCount_++]=e,!e.isBeingObserved_&&u.trackingContext&&(e.isBeingObserved_=!0,e.onBO())),e.isBeingObserved_):(e.observers_.size===0&&u.inBatch>0&&wn(e),!1)}function bn(e){e.lowestObserverState_!==h.STALE_&&(e.lowestObserverState_=h.STALE_,e.observers_.forEach(function(t){t.dependenciesState_===h.UP_TO_DATE_&&t.onBecomeStale_(),t.dependenciesState_=h.STALE_}))}function Qa(e){e.lowestObserverState_!==h.STALE_&&(e.lowestObserverState_=h.STALE_,e.observers_.forEach(function(t){t.dependenciesState_===h.POSSIBLY_STALE_?t.dependenciesState_=h.STALE_:t.dependenciesState_===h.UP_TO_DATE_&&(e.lowestObserverState_=h.UP_TO_DATE_)}))}function Xa(e){e.lowestObserverState_===h.UP_TO_DATE_&&(e.lowestObserverState_=h.POSSIBLY_STALE_,e.observers_.forEach(function(t){t.dependenciesState_===h.UP_TO_DATE_&&(t.dependenciesState_=h.POSSIBLY_STALE_,t.onBecomeStale_())}))}var Ce=function(){function e(a,n,r,o){a===void 0&&(a="Reaction"),this.name_=void 0,this.onInvalidate_=void 0,this.errorHandler_=void 0,this.requiresObservable_=void 0,this.observing_=[],this.newObserving_=[],this.dependenciesState_=h.NOT_TRACKING_,this.diffValue_=0,this.runId_=0,this.unboundDepsCount_=0,this.isDisposed_=!1,this.isScheduled_=!1,this.isTrackPending_=!1,this.isRunning_=!1,this.isTracing_=Pe.NONE,this.name_=a,this.onInvalidate_=n,this.errorHandler_=r,this.requiresObservable_=o}var t=e.prototype;return t.onBecomeStale_=function(){this.schedule_()},t.schedule_=function(){this.isScheduled_||(this.isScheduled_=!0,u.pendingReactions.push(this),An())},t.isScheduled=function(){return this.isScheduled_},t.runReaction_=function(){if(!this.isDisposed_){k(),this.isScheduled_=!1;var n=u.trackingContext;if(u.trackingContext=this,it(this)){this.isTrackPending_=!0;try{this.onInvalidate_()}catch(r){this.reportExceptionInDerivation_(r)}}u.trackingContext=n,S()}},t.track=function(n){if(!this.isDisposed_){k(),this.isRunning_=!0;var r=u.trackingContext;u.trackingContext=this;var o=ln(this,n,void 0);u.trackingContext=r,this.isRunning_=!1,this.isTrackPending_=!1,this.isDisposed_&&st(this),je(o)&&this.reportExceptionInDerivation_(o.cause),S()}},t.reportExceptionInDerivation_=function(n){var r=this;if(this.errorHandler_){this.errorHandler_(n,this);return}if(u.disableErrorBoundaries)throw n;var o="[mobx] uncaught error in '"+this+"'";u.suppressReactionErrors||console.error(o,n),u.globalReactionErrorHandlers.forEach(function(i){return i(n,r)})},t.dispose=function(){this.isDisposed_||(this.isDisposed_=!0,this.isRunning_||(k(),st(this),S()))},t.getDisposer_=function(n){var r=this,o=function i(){r.dispose(),n==null||n.removeEventListener==null||n.removeEventListener("abort",i)};return n==null||n.addEventListener==null||n.addEventListener("abort",o),o[l]=this,o},t.toString=function(){return"Reaction["+this.name_+"]"},t.trace=function(n){},e}(),Za=100,ct=function(t){return t()};function An(){u.inBatch>0||u.isRunningReactions||ct(er)}function er(){u.isRunningReactions=!0;for(var e=u.pendingReactions,t=0;e.length>0;){++t===Za&&(console.error("[mobx] cycle in reaction: "+e[0]),e.splice(0));for(var a=e.splice(0),n=0,r=a.length;n<r;n++)a[n].runReaction_()}u.isRunningReactions=!1}var Ie=K("Reaction",Ce);function tr(e){var t=ct;ct=function(n){return e(function(){return t(n)})}}function le(){return!1}function nr(e){return console.warn("[mobx.spy] Is a no-op in production builds"),function(){}}var _n="action",ar="action.bound",kn="autoAction",rr="autoAction.bound",or="<unnamed action>",Sn=_e(_n),ir=_e(ar,{bound:!0}),Tn=_e(kn,{autoAction:!0}),sr=_e(rr,{autoAction:!0,bound:!0});function Rn(e){var t=function(n,r){if(O(n))return oe(n.name||or,n,e);if(O(r))return oe(n,r,e);if($(r))return be(n,r,e?Tn:Sn);if($(n))return x(_e(e?kn:_n,{name:n,autoAction:e}))};return t}var y=Rn(!1);Object.assign(y,Sn);var pe=Rn(!0);Object.assign(pe,Tn);y.bound=x(ir);pe.bound=x(sr);function bt(e){return O(e)&&e.isMobxAction===!0}function cr(e,t){var a,n,r,o,i;t===void 0&&(t=Ut);var s=(a=(n=t)==null?void 0:n.name)!=null?a:"Autorun",c=!t.scheduler&&!t.delay,d;if(c)d=new Ce(s,function(){this.track(v)},t.onError,t.requiresObservable);else{var f=dr(t),m=!1;d=new Ce(s,function(){m||(m=!0,f(function(){m=!1,d.isDisposed_||d.track(v)}))},t.onError,t.requiresObservable)}function v(){e(d)}return(r=t)!=null&&(o=r.signal)!=null&&o.aborted||d.schedule_(),d.getDisposer_((i=t)==null?void 0:i.signal)}var ur=function(t){return t()};function dr(e){return e.scheduler?e.scheduler:e.delay?function(t){return setTimeout(t,e.delay)}:ur}var fr="onBO",lr="onBUO";function hr(e,t,a){return Mn(fr,e,t,a)}function On(e,t,a){return Mn(lr,e,t,a)}function Mn(e,t,a,n){var r=typeof n=="function"?ie(t,a):ie(t),o=O(n)?n:a,i=e+"L";return r[i]?r[i].add(o):r[i]=new Set([o]),function(){var s=r[i];s&&(s.delete(o),s.size===0&&delete r[i])}}var pr="never",Je="always",mr="observed";function vr(e){e.isolateGlobalState===!0&&za();var t=e.useProxies,a=e.enforceActions;if(t!==void 0&&(u.useProxies=t===Je?!0:t===pr?!1:typeof Proxy<"u"),t==="ifavailable"&&(u.verifyProxies=!0),a!==void 0){var n=a===Je?Je:a===mr;u.enforceActions=n,u.allowStateChanges=!(n===!0||n===Je)}["computedRequiresReaction","reactionRequiresObservable","observableRequiresReaction","disableErrorBoundaries","safeDescriptors"].forEach(function(r){r in e&&(u[r]=!!e[r])}),u.allowStateReads=!u.observableRequiresReaction,e.reactionScheduler&&tr(e.reactionScheduler)}function Jn(e,t,a,n){var r=na(t);return H(function(){var o=Te(e,n)[l];ne(r).forEach(function(i){o.extend_(i,r[i],a&&i in a?a[i]:!0)})}),e}function gr(e,t){return jn(ie(e,t))}function jn(e){var t={name:e.name_};return e.observing_&&e.observing_.length>0&&(t.dependencies=wr(e.observing_).map(jn)),t}function wr(e){return Array.from(new Set(e))}var yr=0;function qn(){this.message="FLOW_CANCELLED"}qn.prototype=Object.create(Error.prototype);var jt=en("flow"),br=en("flow.bound",{bound:!0}),me=Object.assign(function(t,a){if($(a))return be(t,a,jt);var n=t,r=n.name||"<unnamed flow>",o=function(){var s=this,c=arguments,d=++yr,f=y(r+" - runid: "+d+" - init",n).apply(s,c),m,v=void 0,D=new Promise(function(Q,M){var J=0;m=M;function Re(b){v=void 0;var L;try{L=y(r+" - runid: "+d+" - yield "+J++,f.next).call(f,b)}catch(F){return M(F)}de(L)}function Qe(b){v=void 0;var L;try{L=y(r+" - runid: "+d+" - yield "+J++,f.throw).call(f,b)}catch(F){return M(F)}de(L)}function de(b){if(O(b==null?void 0:b.then)){b.then(de,M);return}return b.done?Q(b.value):(v=Promise.resolve(b.value),v.then(Re,Qe))}Re(void 0)});return D.cancel=y(r+" - runid: "+d+" - cancel",function(){try{v&&qt(v);var Q=f.return(void 0),M=Promise.resolve(Q.value);M.then(Z,Z),qt(M),m(new qn)}catch(J){m(J)}}),D};return o.isMobXFlow=!0,o},jt);me.bound=x(br);function qt(e){O(e.cancel)&&e.cancel()}function We(e){return(e==null?void 0:e.isMobXFlow)===!0}function Ar(e,t){return e?t!==void 0?ve(e)?e[l].values_.has(t):!1:ve(e)||!!e[l]||mt(e)||Ie(e)||ze(e):!1}function xn(e){return Ar(e)}function P(e,t){t===void 0&&(t=void 0),k();try{return e.apply(t)}finally{S()}}function X(e){return e[l]}var _r={has:function(t,a){return X(t).has_(a)},get:function(t,a){return X(t).get_(a)},set:function(t,a,n){var r;return $(a)?(r=X(t).set_(a,n,!0))!=null?r:!0:!1},deleteProperty:function(t,a){var n;return $(a)?(n=X(t).delete_(a,!0))!=null?n:!0:!1},defineProperty:function(t,a,n){var r;return(r=X(t).defineProperty_(a,n))!=null?r:!0},ownKeys:function(t){return X(t).ownKeys_()},preventExtensions:function(t){p(13)}};function kr(e,t){var a,n;return Ht(),e=Te(e,t),(n=(a=e[l]).proxy_)!=null?n:a.proxy_=new Proxy(e,_r)}function A(e){return e.interceptors_!==void 0&&e.interceptors_.length>0}function ke(e,t){var a=e.interceptors_||(e.interceptors_=[]);return a.push(t),Ft(function(){var n=a.indexOf(t);n!==-1&&a.splice(n,1)})}function _(e,t){var a=z();try{for(var n=[].concat(e.interceptors_||[]),r=0,o=n.length;r<o&&(t=n[r](t),t&&!t.type&&p(14),!!t);r++);return t}finally{C(a)}}function T(e){return e.changeListeners_!==void 0&&e.changeListeners_.length>0}function Se(e,t){var a=e.changeListeners_||(e.changeListeners_=[]);return a.push(t),Ft(function(){var n=a.indexOf(t);n!==-1&&a.splice(n,1)})}function R(e,t){var a=z(),n=e.changeListeners_;if(n){n=n.slice();for(var r=0,o=n.length;r<o;r++)n[r](t);C(a)}}function Sr(e,t,a){return H(function(){var n,r=Te(e,a)[l];(n=t)!=null||(t=ia(e)),ne(t).forEach(function(o){return r.make_(o,t[o])})}),e}var et=Symbol("mobx-keys");function Tr(e,t,a){return I(e)?Jn(e,e,t,a):(H(function(){var n=Te(e,a)[l];if(!e[et]){var r=Object.getPrototypeOf(e),o=new Set([].concat(ne(e),ne(r)));o.delete("constructor"),o.delete(l),we(r,et,o)}e[et].forEach(function(i){return n.make_(i,t&&i in t?t[i]:!0)})}),e)}var xt="splice",E="update",Rr=1e4,Or={get:function(t,a){var n=t[l];return a===l?n:a==="length"?n.getArrayLength_():typeof a=="string"&&!isNaN(a)?n.get_(parseInt(a)):N(Le,a)?Le[a]:t[a]},set:function(t,a,n){var r=t[l];return a==="length"&&r.setArrayLength_(n),typeof a=="symbol"||isNaN(a)?t[a]=n:r.set_(parseInt(a),n),!0},preventExtensions:function(){p(15)}},At=function(){function e(a,n,r,o){a===void 0&&(a="ObservableArray"),this.owned_=void 0,this.legacyMode_=void 0,this.atom_=void 0,this.values_=[],this.interceptors_=void 0,this.changeListeners_=void 0,this.enhancer_=void 0,this.dehancer=void 0,this.proxy_=void 0,this.lastKnownLength_=0,this.owned_=r,this.legacyMode_=o,this.atom_=new Ae(a),this.enhancer_=function(i,s){return n(i,s,"ObservableArray[..]")}}var t=e.prototype;return t.dehanceValue_=function(n){return this.dehancer!==void 0?this.dehancer(n):n},t.dehanceValues_=function(n){return this.dehancer!==void 0&&n.length>0?n.map(this.dehancer):n},t.intercept_=function(n){return ke(this,n)},t.observe_=function(n,r){return r===void 0&&(r=!1),r&&n({observableKind:"array",object:this.proxy_,debugObjectName:this.atom_.name_,type:"splice",index:0,added:this.values_.slice(),addedCount:this.values_.length,removed:[],removedCount:0}),Se(this,n)},t.getArrayLength_=function(){return this.atom_.reportObserved(),this.values_.length},t.setArrayLength_=function(n){(typeof n!="number"||isNaN(n)||n<0)&&p("Out of range: "+n);var r=this.values_.length;if(n!==r)if(n>r){for(var o=new Array(n-r),i=0;i<n-r;i++)o[i]=void 0;this.spliceWithArray_(r,0,o)}else this.spliceWithArray_(n,r-n)},t.updateArrayLength_=function(n,r){n!==this.lastKnownLength_&&p(16),this.lastKnownLength_+=r,this.legacyMode_&&r>0&&Yn(n+r+1)},t.spliceWithArray_=function(n,r,o){var i=this;this.atom_;var s=this.values_.length;if(n===void 0?n=0:n>s?n=s:n<0&&(n=Math.max(0,s+n)),arguments.length===1?r=s-n:r==null?r=0:r=Math.max(0,Math.min(r,s-n)),o===void 0&&(o=rt),A(this)){var c=_(this,{object:this.proxy_,type:xt,index:n,removedCount:r,added:o});if(!c)return rt;r=c.removedCount,o=c.added}if(o=o.length===0?o:o.map(function(m){return i.enhancer_(m,void 0)}),this.legacyMode_){var d=o.length-r;this.updateArrayLength_(s,d)}var f=this.spliceItemsIntoValues_(n,r,o);return(r!==0||o.length!==0)&&this.notifyArraySplice_(n,o,f),this.dehanceValues_(f)},t.spliceItemsIntoValues_=function(n,r,o){if(o.length<Rr){var i;return(i=this.values_).splice.apply(i,[n,r].concat(o))}else{var s=this.values_.slice(n,n+r),c=this.values_.slice(n+r);this.values_.length+=o.length-r;for(var d=0;d<o.length;d++)this.values_[n+d]=o[d];for(var f=0;f<c.length;f++)this.values_[n+o.length+f]=c[f];return s}},t.notifyArrayChildUpdate_=function(n,r,o){var i=!this.owned_&&le(),s=T(this),c=s||i?{observableKind:"array",object:this.proxy_,type:E,debugObjectName:this.atom_.name_,index:n,newValue:r,oldValue:o}:null;this.atom_.reportChanged(),s&&R(this,c)},t.notifyArraySplice_=function(n,r,o){var i=!this.owned_&&le(),s=T(this),c=s||i?{observableKind:"array",object:this.proxy_,debugObjectName:this.atom_.name_,type:xt,index:n,removed:o,added:r,removedCount:o.length,addedCount:r.length}:null;this.atom_.reportChanged(),s&&R(this,c)},t.get_=function(n){if(this.legacyMode_&&n>=this.values_.length){console.warn("[mobx] Out of bounds read: "+n);return}return this.atom_.reportObserved(),this.dehanceValue_(this.values_[n])},t.set_=function(n,r){var o=this.values_;if(this.legacyMode_&&n>o.length&&p(17,n,o.length),n<o.length){this.atom_;var i=o[n];if(A(this)){var s=_(this,{type:E,object:this.proxy_,index:n,newValue:r});if(!s)return;r=s.newValue}r=this.enhancer_(r,i);var c=r!==i;c&&(o[n]=r,this.notifyArrayChildUpdate_(n,r,i))}else{for(var d=new Array(n+1-o.length),f=0;f<d.length-1;f++)d[f]=void 0;d[d.length-1]=r,this.spliceWithArray_(o.length,0,d)}},e}();function Mr(e,t,a,n){return a===void 0&&(a="ObservableArray"),n===void 0&&(n=!1),Ht(),H(function(){var r=new At(a,t,n,!1);Kt(r.values_,l,r);var o=new Proxy(r.values_,Or);return r.proxy_=o,e&&e.length&&r.spliceWithArray_(0,0,e),o})}var Le={clear:function(){return this.splice(0)},replace:function(t){var a=this[l];return a.spliceWithArray_(0,a.values_.length,t)},toJSON:function(){return this.slice()},splice:function(t,a){for(var n=arguments.length,r=new Array(n>2?n-2:0),o=2;o<n;o++)r[o-2]=arguments[o];var i=this[l];switch(arguments.length){case 0:return[];case 1:return i.spliceWithArray_(t);case 2:return i.spliceWithArray_(t,a)}return i.spliceWithArray_(t,a,r)},spliceWithArray:function(t,a,n){return this[l].spliceWithArray_(t,a,n)},push:function(){for(var t=this[l],a=arguments.length,n=new Array(a),r=0;r<a;r++)n[r]=arguments[r];return t.spliceWithArray_(t.values_.length,0,n),t.values_.length},pop:function(){return this.splice(Math.max(this[l].values_.length-1,0),1)[0]},shift:function(){return this.splice(0,1)[0]},unshift:function(){for(var t=this[l],a=arguments.length,n=new Array(a),r=0;r<a;r++)n[r]=arguments[r];return t.spliceWithArray_(0,0,n),t.values_.length},reverse:function(){return u.trackingDerivation&&p(37,"reverse"),this.replace(this.slice().reverse()),this},sort:function(){u.trackingDerivation&&p(37,"sort");var t=this.slice();return t.sort.apply(t,arguments),this.replace(t),this},remove:function(t){var a=this[l],n=a.dehanceValues_(a.values_).indexOf(t);return n>-1?(this.splice(n,1),!0):!1}};w("concat",W);w("flat",W);w("includes",W);w("indexOf",W);w("join",W);w("lastIndexOf",W);w("slice",W);w("toString",W);w("toLocaleString",W);w("every",U);w("filter",U);w("find",U);w("findIndex",U);w("flatMap",U);w("forEach",U);w("map",U);w("some",U);w("reduce",En);w("reduceRight",En);function w(e,t){typeof Array.prototype[e]=="function"&&(Le[e]=t(e))}function W(e){return function(){var t=this[l];t.atom_.reportObserved();var a=t.dehanceValues_(t.values_);return a[e].apply(a,arguments)}}function U(e){return function(t,a){var n=this,r=this[l];r.atom_.reportObserved();var o=r.dehanceValues_(r.values_);return o[e](function(i,s){return t.call(a,i,s,n)})}}function En(e){return function(){var t=this,a=this[l];a.atom_.reportObserved();var n=a.dehanceValues_(a.values_),r=arguments[0];return arguments[0]=function(o,i,s){return r(o,i,s,t)},n[e].apply(n,arguments)}}var Jr=K("ObservableArrayAdministration",At);function Ge(e){return He(e)&&Jr(e[l])}var Dn,Bn,jr={},V="add",Ve="delete";Dn=Symbol.iterator;Bn=Symbol.toStringTag;var Pn=function(){function e(a,n,r){var o=this;n===void 0&&(n=re),r===void 0&&(r="ObservableMap"),this.enhancer_=void 0,this.name_=void 0,this[l]=jr,this.data_=void 0,this.hasMap_=void 0,this.keysAtom_=void 0,this.interceptors_=void 0,this.changeListeners_=void 0,this.dehancer=void 0,this.enhancer_=n,this.name_=r,O(Map)||p(18),H(function(){o.keysAtom_=Xt("ObservableMap.keys()"),o.data_=new Map,o.hasMap_=new Map,a&&o.merge(a)})}var t=e.prototype;return t.has_=function(n){return this.data_.has(n)},t.has=function(n){var r=this;if(!u.trackingDerivation)return this.has_(n);var o=this.hasMap_.get(n);if(!o){var i=o=new te(this.has_(n),Fe,"ObservableMap.key?",!1);this.hasMap_.set(n,i),On(i,function(){return r.hasMap_.delete(n)})}return o.get()},t.set=function(n,r){var o=this.has_(n);if(A(this)){var i=_(this,{type:o?E:V,object:this,newValue:r,name:n});if(!i)return this;r=i.newValue}return o?this.updateValue_(n,r):this.addValue_(n,r),this},t.delete=function(n){var r=this;if(this.keysAtom_,A(this)){var o=_(this,{type:Ve,object:this,name:n});if(!o)return!1}if(this.has_(n)){var i=le(),s=T(this),c=s||i?{observableKind:"map",debugObjectName:this.name_,type:Ve,object:this,oldValue:this.data_.get(n).value_,name:n}:null;return P(function(){var d;r.keysAtom_.reportChanged(),(d=r.hasMap_.get(n))==null||d.setNewValue_(!1);var f=r.data_.get(n);f.setNewValue_(void 0),r.data_.delete(n)}),s&&R(this,c),!0}return!1},t.updateValue_=function(n,r){var o=this.data_.get(n);if(r=o.prepareNewValue_(r),r!==u.UNCHANGED){var i=le(),s=T(this),c=s||i?{observableKind:"map",debugObjectName:this.name_,type:E,object:this,oldValue:o.value_,name:n,newValue:r}:null;o.setNewValue_(r),s&&R(this,c)}},t.addValue_=function(n,r){var o=this;this.keysAtom_,P(function(){var d,f=new te(r,o.enhancer_,"ObservableMap.key",!1);o.data_.set(n,f),r=f.value_,(d=o.hasMap_.get(n))==null||d.setNewValue_(!0),o.keysAtom_.reportChanged()});var i=le(),s=T(this),c=s||i?{observableKind:"map",debugObjectName:this.name_,type:V,object:this,name:n,newValue:r}:null;s&&R(this,c)},t.get=function(n){return this.has(n)?this.dehanceValue_(this.data_.get(n).get()):this.dehanceValue_(void 0)},t.dehanceValue_=function(n){return this.dehancer!==void 0?this.dehancer(n):n},t.keys=function(){return this.keysAtom_.reportObserved(),this.data_.keys()},t.values=function(){var n=this,r=this.keys();return ge({next:function(){var i=r.next(),s=i.done,c=i.value;return{done:s,value:s?void 0:n.get(c)}}})},t.entries=function(){var n=this,r=this.keys();return ge({next:function(){var i=r.next(),s=i.done,c=i.value;return{done:s,value:s?void 0:[c,n.get(c)]}}})},t[Dn]=function(){return this.entries()},t.forEach=function(n,r){for(var o=ee(this),i;!(i=o()).done;){var s=i.value,c=s[0],d=s[1];n.call(r,d,c,this)}},t.merge=function(n){var r=this;return G(n)&&(n=new Map(n)),P(function(){I(n)?ta(n).forEach(function(o){return r.set(o,n[o])}):Array.isArray(n)?n.forEach(function(o){var i=o[0],s=o[1];return r.set(i,s)}):ce(n)?(n.constructor!==Map&&p(19,n),n.forEach(function(o,i){return r.set(i,o)})):n!=null&&p(20,n)}),this},t.clear=function(){var n=this;P(function(){hn(function(){for(var r=ee(n.keys()),o;!(o=r()).done;){var i=o.value;n.delete(i)}})})},t.replace=function(n){var r=this;return P(function(){for(var o=qr(n),i=new Map,s=!1,c=ee(r.data_.keys()),d;!(d=c()).done;){var f=d.value;if(!o.has(f)){var m=r.delete(f);if(m)s=!0;else{var v=r.data_.get(f);i.set(f,v)}}}for(var D=ee(o.entries()),Q;!(Q=D()).done;){var M=Q.value,J=M[0],Re=M[1],Qe=r.data_.has(J);if(r.set(J,Re),r.data_.has(J)){var de=r.data_.get(J);i.set(J,de),Qe||(s=!0)}}if(!s)if(r.data_.size!==i.size)r.keysAtom_.reportChanged();else for(var b=r.data_.keys(),L=i.keys(),F=b.next(),St=L.next();!F.done;){if(F.value!==St.value){r.keysAtom_.reportChanged();break}F=b.next(),St=L.next()}r.data_=i}),this},t.toString=function(){return"[object ObservableMap]"},t.toJSON=function(){return Array.from(this)},t.observe_=function(n,r){return Se(this,n)},t.intercept_=function(n){return ke(this,n)},pt(e,[{key:"size",get:function(){return this.keysAtom_.reportObserved(),this.data_.size}},{key:Bn,get:function(){return"Map"}}]),e}(),G=K("ObservableMap",Pn);function qr(e){if(ce(e)||G(e))return e;if(Array.isArray(e))return new Map(e);if(I(e)){var t=new Map;for(var a in e)t.set(a,e[a]);return t}else return p(21,e)}var Nn,Cn,xr={};Nn=Symbol.iterator;Cn=Symbol.toStringTag;var In=function(){function e(a,n,r){var o=this;n===void 0&&(n=re),r===void 0&&(r="ObservableSet"),this.name_=void 0,this[l]=xr,this.data_=new Set,this.atom_=void 0,this.changeListeners_=void 0,this.interceptors_=void 0,this.dehancer=void 0,this.enhancer_=void 0,this.name_=r,O(Set)||p(22),this.enhancer_=function(i,s){return n(i,s,r)},H(function(){o.atom_=Xt(o.name_),a&&o.replace(a)})}var t=e.prototype;return t.dehanceValue_=function(n){return this.dehancer!==void 0?this.dehancer(n):n},t.clear=function(){var n=this;P(function(){hn(function(){for(var r=ee(n.data_.values()),o;!(o=r()).done;){var i=o.value;n.delete(i)}})})},t.forEach=function(n,r){for(var o=ee(this),i;!(i=o()).done;){var s=i.value;n.call(r,s,s,this)}},t.add=function(n){var r=this;if(this.atom_,A(this)){var o=_(this,{type:V,object:this,newValue:n});if(!o)return this}if(!this.has(n)){P(function(){r.data_.add(r.enhancer_(n,void 0)),r.atom_.reportChanged()});var i=!1,s=T(this),c=s||i?{observableKind:"set",debugObjectName:this.name_,type:V,object:this,newValue:n}:null;s&&R(this,c)}return this},t.delete=function(n){var r=this;if(A(this)){var o=_(this,{type:Ve,object:this,oldValue:n});if(!o)return!1}if(this.has(n)){var i=!1,s=T(this),c=s||i?{observableKind:"set",debugObjectName:this.name_,type:Ve,object:this,oldValue:n}:null;return P(function(){r.atom_.reportChanged(),r.data_.delete(n)}),s&&R(this,c),!0}return!1},t.has=function(n){return this.atom_.reportObserved(),this.data_.has(this.dehanceValue_(n))},t.entries=function(){var n=0,r=Array.from(this.keys()),o=Array.from(this.values());return ge({next:function(){var s=n;return n+=1,s<o.length?{value:[r[s],o[s]],done:!1}:{done:!0}}})},t.keys=function(){return this.values()},t.values=function(){this.atom_.reportObserved();var n=this,r=0,o=Array.from(this.data_.values());return ge({next:function(){return r<o.length?{value:n.dehanceValue_(o[r++]),done:!1}:{done:!0}}})},t.replace=function(n){var r=this;return ue(n)&&(n=new Set(n)),P(function(){Array.isArray(n)?(r.clear(),n.forEach(function(o){return r.add(o)})):ye(n)?(r.clear(),n.forEach(function(o){return r.add(o)})):n!=null&&p("Cannot initialize set from "+n)}),this},t.observe_=function(n,r){return Se(this,n)},t.intercept_=function(n){return ke(this,n)},t.toJSON=function(){return Array.from(this)},t.toString=function(){return"[object ObservableSet]"},t[Nn]=function(){return this.values()},pt(e,[{key:"size",get:function(){return this.atom_.reportObserved(),this.data_.size}},{key:Cn,get:function(){return"Set"}}]),e}(),ue=K("ObservableSet",In),Et=Object.create(null),Dt="remove",Wn=function(){function e(a,n,r,o){n===void 0&&(n=new Map),o===void 0&&(o=Ma),this.target_=void 0,this.values_=void 0,this.name_=void 0,this.defaultAnnotation_=void 0,this.keysAtom_=void 0,this.changeListeners_=void 0,this.interceptors_=void 0,this.proxy_=void 0,this.isPlainObject_=void 0,this.appliedAnnotations_=void 0,this.pendingKeys_=void 0,this.target_=a,this.values_=n,this.name_=r,this.defaultAnnotation_=o,this.keysAtom_=new Ae("ObservableObject.keys"),this.isPlainObject_=I(this.target_)}var t=e.prototype;return t.getObservablePropValue_=function(n){return this.values_.get(n).get()},t.setObservablePropValue_=function(n,r){var o=this.values_.get(n);if(o instanceof he)return o.set(r),!0;if(A(this)){var i=_(this,{type:E,object:this.proxy_||this.target_,name:n,newValue:r});if(!i)return null;r=i.newValue}if(r=o.prepareNewValue_(r),r!==u.UNCHANGED){var s=T(this),c=!1,d=s||c?{type:E,observableKind:"object",debugObjectName:this.name_,object:this.proxy_||this.target_,oldValue:o.value_,name:n,newValue:r}:null;o.setNewValue_(r),s&&R(this,d)}return!0},t.get_=function(n){return u.trackingDerivation&&!N(this.target_,n)&&this.has_(n),this.target_[n]},t.set_=function(n,r,o){return o===void 0&&(o=!1),N(this.target_,n)?this.values_.has(n)?this.setObservablePropValue_(n,r):o?Reflect.set(this.target_,n,r):(this.target_[n]=r,!0):this.extend_(n,{value:r,enumerable:!0,writable:!0,configurable:!0},this.defaultAnnotation_,o)},t.has_=function(n){if(!u.trackingDerivation)return n in this.target_;this.pendingKeys_||(this.pendingKeys_=new Map);var r=this.pendingKeys_.get(n);return r||(r=new te(n in this.target_,Fe,"ObservableObject.key?",!1),this.pendingKeys_.set(n,r)),r.get()},t.make_=function(n,r){if(r===!0&&(r=this.defaultAnnotation_),r!==!1){if(!(n in this.target_)){var o;if((o=this.target_[j])!=null&&o[n])return;p(1,r.annotationType_,this.name_+"."+n.toString())}for(var i=this.target_;i&&i!==Ue;){var s=Ee(i,n);if(s){var c=r.make_(this,n,s,i);if(c===0)return;if(c===1)break}i=Object.getPrototypeOf(i)}Pt(this,r,n)}},t.extend_=function(n,r,o,i){if(i===void 0&&(i=!1),o===!0&&(o=this.defaultAnnotation_),o===!1)return this.defineProperty_(n,r,i);var s=o.extend_(this,n,r,i);return s&&Pt(this,o,n),s},t.defineProperty_=function(n,r,o){o===void 0&&(o=!1),this.keysAtom_;try{k();var i=this.delete_(n);if(!i)return i;if(A(this)){var s=_(this,{object:this.proxy_||this.target_,name:n,type:V,newValue:r.value});if(!s)return null;var c=s.newValue;r.value!==c&&(r=ae({},r,{value:c}))}if(o){if(!Reflect.defineProperty(this.target_,n,r))return!1}else q(this.target_,n,r);this.notifyPropertyAddition_(n,r.value)}finally{S()}return!0},t.defineObservableProperty_=function(n,r,o,i){i===void 0&&(i=!1),this.keysAtom_;try{k();var s=this.delete_(n);if(!s)return s;if(A(this)){var c=_(this,{object:this.proxy_||this.target_,name:n,type:V,newValue:r});if(!c)return null;r=c.newValue}var d=Bt(n),f={configurable:u.safeDescriptors?this.isPlainObject_:!0,enumerable:!0,get:d.get,set:d.set};if(i){if(!Reflect.defineProperty(this.target_,n,f))return!1}else q(this.target_,n,f);var m=new te(r,o,"ObservableObject.key",!1);this.values_.set(n,m),this.notifyPropertyAddition_(n,m.value_)}finally{S()}return!0},t.defineComputedProperty_=function(n,r,o){o===void 0&&(o=!1),this.keysAtom_;try{k();var i=this.delete_(n);if(!i)return i;if(A(this)){var s=_(this,{object:this.proxy_||this.target_,name:n,type:V,newValue:void 0});if(!s)return null}r.name||(r.name="ObservableObject.key"),r.context=this.proxy_||this.target_;var c=Bt(n),d={configurable:u.safeDescriptors?this.isPlainObject_:!0,enumerable:!1,get:c.get,set:c.set};if(o){if(!Reflect.defineProperty(this.target_,n,d))return!1}else q(this.target_,n,d);this.values_.set(n,new he(r)),this.notifyPropertyAddition_(n,void 0)}finally{S()}return!0},t.delete_=function(n,r){if(r===void 0&&(r=!1),this.keysAtom_,!N(this.target_,n))return!0;if(A(this)){var o=_(this,{object:this.proxy_||this.target_,name:n,type:Dt});if(!o)return null}try{var i,s;k();var c=T(this),d=!1,f=this.values_.get(n),m=void 0;if(!f&&(c||d)){var v;m=(v=Ee(this.target_,n))==null?void 0:v.value}if(r){if(!Reflect.deleteProperty(this.target_,n))return!1}else delete this.target_[n];if(f&&(this.values_.delete(n),f instanceof te&&(m=f.value_),bn(f)),this.keysAtom_.reportChanged(),(i=this.pendingKeys_)==null||(s=i.get(n))==null||s.set(n in this.target_),c||d){var D={type:Dt,observableKind:"object",object:this.proxy_||this.target_,debugObjectName:this.name_,oldValue:m,name:n};c&&R(this,D)}}finally{S()}return!0},t.observe_=function(n,r){return Se(this,n)},t.intercept_=function(n){return ke(this,n)},t.notifyPropertyAddition_=function(n,r){var o,i,s=T(this),c=!1;if(s||c){var d=s||c?{type:V,observableKind:"object",debugObjectName:this.name_,object:this.proxy_||this.target_,name:n,newValue:r}:null;s&&R(this,d)}(o=this.pendingKeys_)==null||(i=o.get(n))==null||i.set(!0),this.keysAtom_.reportChanged()},t.ownKeys_=function(){return this.keysAtom_.reportObserved(),ne(this.target_)},t.keys_=function(){return this.keysAtom_.reportObserved(),Object.keys(this.target_)},e}();function Te(e,t){var a;if(N(e,l))return e;var n=(a=t==null?void 0:t.name)!=null?a:"ObservableObject",r=new Wn(e,new Map,String(n),Ca(t));return we(e,l,r),e}var Er=K("ObservableObjectAdministration",Wn);function Bt(e){return Et[e]||(Et[e]={get:function(){return this[l].getObservablePropValue_(e)},set:function(a){return this[l].setObservablePropValue_(e,a)}})}function ve(e){return He(e)?Er(e[l]):!1}function Pt(e,t,a){var n;(n=e.target_[j])==null||delete n[a]}var Dr=Vn(0),Br=function(){var e=!1,t={};return Object.defineProperty(t,"0",{set:function(){e=!0}}),Object.create(t)[0]=1,e===!1}(),tt=0,Ln=function(){};function Pr(e,t){Object.setPrototypeOf?Object.setPrototypeOf(e.prototype,t):e.prototype.__proto__!==void 0?e.prototype.__proto__=t:e.prototype=t}Pr(Ln,Array.prototype);var _t=function(e,t,a){Qt(n,e);function n(o,i,s,c){var d;return s===void 0&&(s="ObservableArray"),c===void 0&&(c=!1),d=e.call(this)||this,H(function(){var f=new At(s,i,c,!0);f.proxy_=Ze(d),Kt(Ze(d),l,f),o&&o.length&&d.spliceWithArray(0,0,o),Br&&Object.defineProperty(Ze(d),"0",Dr)}),d}var r=n.prototype;return r.concat=function(){this[l].atom_.reportObserved();for(var i=arguments.length,s=new Array(i),c=0;c<i;c++)s[c]=arguments[c];return Array.prototype.concat.apply(this.slice(),s.map(function(d){return Ge(d)?d.slice():d}))},r[a]=function(){var o=this,i=0;return ge({next:function(){return i<o.length?{value:o[i++],done:!1}:{done:!0,value:void 0}}})},pt(n,[{key:"length",get:function(){return this[l].getArrayLength_()},set:function(i){this[l].setArrayLength_(i)}},{key:t,get:function(){return"Array"}}]),n}(Ln,Symbol.toStringTag,Symbol.iterator);Object.entries(Le).forEach(function(e){var t=e[0],a=e[1];t!=="concat"&&we(_t.prototype,t,a)});function Vn(e){return{enumerable:!1,configurable:!0,get:function(){return this[l].get_(e)},set:function(a){this[l].set_(e,a)}}}function Nr(e){q(_t.prototype,""+e,Vn(e))}function Yn(e){if(e>tt){for(var t=tt;t<e+100;t++)Nr(t);tt=e}}Yn(1e3);function Cr(e,t,a){return new _t(e,t,a)}function ie(e,t){if(typeof e=="object"&&e!==null){if(Ge(e))return t!==void 0&&p(23),e[l].atom_;if(ue(e))return e.atom_;if(G(e)){if(t===void 0)return e.keysAtom_;var a=e.data_.get(t)||e.hasMap_.get(t);return a||p(25,t,ut(e)),a}if(ve(e)){if(!t)return p(26);var n=e[l].values_.get(t);return n||p(27,t,ut(e)),n}if(mt(e)||ze(e)||Ie(e))return e}else if(O(e)&&Ie(e[l]))return e[l];p(28)}function Un(e,t){if(e||p(29),t!==void 0)return Un(ie(e,t));if(mt(e)||ze(e)||Ie(e)||G(e)||ue(e))return e;if(e[l])return e[l];p(24,e)}function ut(e,t){var a;if(t!==void 0)a=ie(e,t);else{if(bt(e))return e.name;ve(e)||G(e)||ue(e)?a=Un(e):a=ie(e)}return a.name_}function H(e){var t=z(),a=gt(!0);k();try{return e()}finally{S(),wt(a),C(t)}}var Nt=Ue.toString;function kt(e,t,a){return a===void 0&&(a=-1),dt(e,t,a)}function dt(e,t,a,n,r){if(e===t)return e!==0||1/e===1/t;if(e==null||t==null)return!1;if(e!==e)return t!==t;var o=typeof e;if(o!=="function"&&o!=="object"&&typeof t!="object")return!1;var i=Nt.call(e);if(i!==Nt.call(t))return!1;switch(i){case"[object RegExp]":case"[object String]":return""+e==""+t;case"[object Number]":return+e!=+e?+t!=+t:+e==0?1/+e===1/t:+e==+t;case"[object Date]":case"[object Boolean]":return+e==+t;case"[object Symbol]":return typeof Symbol<"u"&&Symbol.valueOf.call(e)===Symbol.valueOf.call(t);case"[object Map]":case"[object Set]":a>=0&&a++;break}e=Ct(e),t=Ct(t);var s=i==="[object Array]";if(!s){if(typeof e!="object"||typeof t!="object")return!1;var c=e.constructor,d=t.constructor;if(c!==d&&!(O(c)&&c instanceof c&&O(d)&&d instanceof d)&&"constructor"in e&&"constructor"in t)return!1}if(a===0)return!1;a<0&&(a=-1),n=n||[],r=r||[];for(var f=n.length;f--;)if(n[f]===e)return r[f]===t;if(n.push(e),r.push(t),s){if(f=e.length,f!==t.length)return!1;for(;f--;)if(!dt(e[f],t[f],a-1,n,r))return!1}else{var m=Object.keys(e),v;if(f=m.length,Object.keys(t).length!==f)return!1;for(;f--;)if(v=m[f],!(N(t,v)&&dt(e[v],t[v],a-1,n,r)))return!1}return n.pop(),r.pop(),!0}function Ct(e){return Ge(e)?e.slice():ce(e)||G(e)||ye(e)||ue(e)?Array.from(e.entries()):e}function ge(e){return e[Symbol.iterator]=Ir,e}function Ir(){return this}["Symbol","Map","Set"].forEach(function(e){var t=ht();typeof t[e]>"u"&&p("MobX requires global '"+e+"' to be available or polyfilled")});typeof __MOBX_DEVTOOLS_GLOBAL_HOOK__=="object"&&__MOBX_DEVTOOLS_GLOBAL_HOOK__.injectMobx({spy:nr,extras:{getDebugName:ut},$mobx:l});if(!Y.useState)throw new Error("mobx-react-lite requires React with Hooks support");if(!Sr)throw new Error("mobx-react-lite@3 requires mobx at least version 6 to be available");function Wr(e){e()}function Lr(e){e||(e=Wr),vr({reactionScheduler:e})}function Vr(e){return gr(e)}var Yr=1e4,Ur=1e4,Hr=function(){function e(t){var a=this;Object.defineProperty(this,"finalize",{enumerable:!0,configurable:!0,writable:!0,value:t}),Object.defineProperty(this,"registrations",{enumerable:!0,configurable:!0,writable:!0,value:new Map}),Object.defineProperty(this,"sweepTimeout",{enumerable:!0,configurable:!0,writable:!0,value:void 0}),Object.defineProperty(this,"sweep",{enumerable:!0,configurable:!0,writable:!0,value:function(n){n===void 0&&(n=Yr),clearTimeout(a.sweepTimeout),a.sweepTimeout=void 0;var r=Date.now();a.registrations.forEach(function(o,i){r-o.registeredAt>=n&&(a.finalize(o.value),a.registrations.delete(i))}),a.registrations.size>0&&a.scheduleSweep()}}),Object.defineProperty(this,"finalizeAllImmediately",{enumerable:!0,configurable:!0,writable:!0,value:function(){a.sweep(0)}})}return Object.defineProperty(e.prototype,"register",{enumerable:!1,configurable:!0,writable:!0,value:function(t,a,n){this.registrations.set(n,{value:a,registeredAt:Date.now()}),this.scheduleSweep()}}),Object.defineProperty(e.prototype,"unregister",{enumerable:!1,configurable:!0,writable:!0,value:function(t){this.registrations.delete(t)}}),Object.defineProperty(e.prototype,"scheduleSweep",{enumerable:!1,configurable:!0,writable:!0,value:function(){this.sweepTimeout===void 0&&(this.sweepTimeout=setTimeout(this.sweep,Ur))}}),e}(),Fr=typeof FinalizationRegistry<"u"?FinalizationRegistry:Hr,ft=new Fr(function(e){var t;(t=e.reaction)===null||t===void 0||t.dispose(),e.reaction=null}),Hn={exports:{}},Fn={};/**
 * @license React
 * use-sync-external-store-shim.production.min.js
 *
 * Copyright (c) Facebook, Inc. and its affiliates.
 *
 * This source code is licensed under the MIT license found in the
 * LICENSE file in the root directory of this source tree.
 */var se=Y;function $r(e,t){return e===t&&(e!==0||1/e===1/t)||e!==e&&t!==t}var Kr=typeof Object.is=="function"?Object.is:$r,zr=se.useState,Gr=se.useEffect,Qr=se.useLayoutEffect,Xr=se.useDebugValue;function Zr(e,t){var a=t(),n=zr({inst:{value:a,getSnapshot:t}}),r=n[0].inst,o=n[1];return Qr(function(){r.value=a,r.getSnapshot=t,nt(r)&&o({inst:r})},[e,a,t]),Gr(function(){return nt(r)&&o({inst:r}),e(function(){nt(r)&&o({inst:r})})},[e]),Xr(a),a}function nt(e){var t=e.getSnapshot;e=e.value;try{var a=t();return!Kr(e,a)}catch{return!0}}function eo(e,t){return t()}var to=typeof window>"u"||typeof window.document>"u"||typeof window.document.createElement>"u"?eo:Zr;Fn.useSyncExternalStore=se.useSyncExternalStore!==void 0?se.useSyncExternalStore:to;Hn.exports=Fn;var no=Hn.exports,ao=globalThis&&globalThis.__read||function(e,t){var a=typeof Symbol=="function"&&e[Symbol.iterator];if(!a)return e;var n=a.call(e),r,o=[],i;try{for(;(t===void 0||t-- >0)&&!(r=n.next()).done;)o.push(r.value)}catch(s){i={error:s}}finally{try{r&&!r.done&&(a=n.return)&&a.call(n)}finally{if(i)throw i.error}}return o},ro=function(){},$n=typeof vn().stateVersion<"u";function It(e){e.reaction=new Ce("observer".concat(e.name),function(){var t;$n||(e.stateVersion=Symbol()),(t=e.onStoreChange)===null||t===void 0||t.call(e)})}function oo(e,t){t===void 0&&(t="observed");var a=Xe.useRef(null),n=ao(Xe.useState(),2),r=n[1];if(!a.current){var o={reaction:null,onStoreChange:null,stateVersion:Symbol(),name:t,subscribe:function(d){return ft.unregister(o),o.onStoreChange=d,o.reaction||(It(o),r(Symbol())),function(){var f;o.onStoreChange=null,(f=o.reaction)===null||f===void 0||f.dispose(),o.reaction=null}},getSnapshot:function(){return $n?vn().stateVersion:o.stateVersion}};a.current=o}var i=a.current;i.reaction||(It(i),ft.register(a,i,i)),Xe.useDebugValue(i.reaction,Vr),no.useSyncExternalStore(i.subscribe,i.getSnapshot,ro);var s,c;if(i.reaction.track(function(){try{s=e()}catch(d){c=d}}),c)throw c;return s}var Kn=typeof Symbol=="function"&&Symbol.for,Wt=Kn?Symbol.for("react.forward_ref"):typeof Y.forwardRef=="function"&&Y.forwardRef(function(e){return null}).$$typeof,Lt=Kn?Symbol.for("react.memo"):typeof Y.memo=="function"&&Y.memo(function(e){return null}).$$typeof;function fo(e,t){var a;if(Lt&&e.$$typeof===Lt)throw new Error("[mobx-react-lite] You are trying to use `observer` on a function component wrapped in either another `observer` or `React.memo`. The observer already applies 'React.memo' for you.");var n=(a=t==null?void 0:t.forwardRef)!==null&&a!==void 0?a:!1,r=e,o=e.displayName||e.name;if(Wt&&e.$$typeof===Wt&&(n=!0,r=e.render,typeof r!="function"))throw new Error("[mobx-react-lite] `render` property of ForwardRef was not a function");var i=function(s,c){return oo(function(){return r(s,c)},o)};return i.displayName=e.displayName,Object.defineProperty(i,"name",{value:e.name,writable:!0,configurable:!0}),e.contextTypes&&(i.contextTypes=e.contextTypes),n&&(i=Y.forwardRef(i)),i=Y.memo(i),so(e,i),i}var io={$$typeof:!0,render:!0,compare:!0,type:!0,displayName:!0};function so(e,t){Object.keys(e).forEach(function(a){io[a]||Object.defineProperty(t,a,Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptor(e,a))})}globalThis&&globalThis.__read;var at;Lr(Qn.unstable_batchedUpdates);at=ft.finalizeAllImmediately;const Vt=[{id:235871649320,category:"JavaScript",topic:"JavaScript Basics",question:"What is JavaScript used for?",answers:{answer:"JavaScript is used for adding interactivity and behavior to websites.",fakeAnswer1:"JavaScript is used for creating databases.",fakeAnswer2:"JavaScript is used for styling web pages.",fakeAnswer3:"JavaScript is used for server-side scripting."}},{id:874962135089,category:"JavaScript",topic:"JavaScript Basics",question:"What is a variable in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"A variable is a container for storing data values.",fakeAnswer1:"A variable is a type of loop in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer2:"A variable is used to define a function in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer3:"A variable is used for conditional statements in JavaScript."}},{id:509218764356,category:"JavaScript",topic:"JavaScript Basics",question:"How do you declare a variable in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"You can declare a variable using the 'var', 'let', or 'const' keyword.",fakeAnswer1:"You can declare a variable using the 'variable' keyword.",fakeAnswer2:"You can declare a variable using the 'value' keyword.",fakeAnswer3:"You can declare a variable using the 'data' keyword."}},{id:621789530482,category:"JavaScript",topic:"JavaScript Basics",question:"What is the difference between 'let' and 'const' in variable declaration?",answers:{answer:"'let' allows variable values to be changed, while 'const' does not allow reassignment.",fakeAnswer1:"'let' is used for integers, and 'const' is used for strings.",fakeAnswer2:"'let' is used for global variables, and 'const' is used for local variables.",fakeAnswer3:"'let' is used for functions, and 'const' is used for loops."}},{id:836942175780,category:"JavaScript",topic:"JavaScript Basics",question:"What is the 'typeof' operator used for?",answers:{answer:"The 'typeof' operator is used to determine the data type of a variable or expression.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'typeof' operator is used to create variables.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'typeof' operator is used to add two numbers together.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'typeof' operator is used to style HTML elements."}},{id:419563287610,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Variables and Data Types",question:"What are the basic data types in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"The basic data types in JavaScript are number, string, boolean, null, undefined, and object.",fakeAnswer1:"The basic data types in JavaScript are array, object, function, and element.",fakeAnswer2:"The basic data types in JavaScript are integer, string, boolean, and character.",fakeAnswer3:"The basic data types in JavaScript are variable, function, object, and array."}},{id:723986154087,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Variables and Data Types",question:"How do you declare a string variable in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"You can declare a string variable by enclosing the text in single or double quotes.",fakeAnswer1:"You can declare a string variable using the 'str' keyword.",fakeAnswer2:"You can declare a string variable using the 'text' keyword.",fakeAnswer3:"You can declare a string variable using the 'string' keyword."}},{id:162594730985,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Variables and Data Types",question:"What is a boolean variable?",answers:{answer:"A boolean variable can only have two values: true or false.",fakeAnswer1:"A boolean variable can have any numeric value.",fakeAnswer2:"A boolean variable can have any string value.",fakeAnswer3:"A boolean variable can have multiple values."}},{id:397861524093,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Variables and Data Types",question:"What is the result of 5 + '5' in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"The result is '55' because JavaScript performs type coercion and converts the number to a string.",fakeAnswer1:"The result is 10 because JavaScript adds the numbers together.",fakeAnswer2:"The result is an error because you cannot add a number and a string in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer3:"The result is '10' because JavaScript converts the string to a number and adds them."}},{id:485179326041,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Variables and Data Types",question:"What is a null value in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"A null value represents the intentional absence of any object value or no value at all.",fakeAnswer1:"A null value is the same as zero in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer2:"A null value represents a missing variable.",fakeAnswer3:"A null value represents a boolean 'false' value."}},{id:730816495321,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Control Structures",question:"What is an 'if' statement used for in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"An 'if' statement is used to execute a block of code if a specified condition is true.",fakeAnswer1:"An 'if' statement is used to declare variables in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer2:"An 'if' statement is used to create arrays in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer3:"An 'if' statement is used to define functions in JavaScript."}},{id:845162730981,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Control Structures",question:"What is the 'else' statement used for in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"The 'else' statement is used to execute a block of code if the 'if' condition is false.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'else' statement is used to create arrays in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'else' statement is used to define functions in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'else' statement is used to declare variables in JavaScript."}},{id:963472518204,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Control Structures",question:"What is a 'for' loop in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"A 'for' loop is used to repeatedly execute a block of code a specified number of times.",fakeAnswer1:"A 'for' loop is used to declare variables in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer2:"A 'for' loop is used to create arrays in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer3:"A 'for' loop is used to define functions in JavaScript."}},{id:582730916374,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Control Structures",question:"What is the purpose of the 'break' statement in a loop?",answers:{answer:"The 'break' statement is used to exit a loop prematurely before its normal termination.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'break' statement is used to define functions in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'break' statement is used to create arrays in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'break' statement is used to declare variables in JavaScript."}},{id:375290186473,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Control Structures",question:"What is a 'switch' statement in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"A 'switch' statement is used to select one of many code blocks to be executed.",fakeAnswer1:"A 'switch' statement is used to declare variables in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer2:"A 'switch' statement is used to create arrays in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer3:"A 'switch' statement is used to define functions in JavaScript."}},{id:134869752031,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Functions and Scope",question:"What is a function in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"A function is a reusable block of code that performs a specific task.",fakeAnswer1:"A function is a variable in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer2:"A function is an array in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer3:"A function is a data type in JavaScript."}},{id:628935471209,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Functions and Scope",question:"How do you define a function in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"You can define a function using the 'function' keyword followed by a function name and parameters.",fakeAnswer1:"You can define a function using the 'var' keyword.",fakeAnswer2:"You can define a function using the 'const' keyword.",fakeAnswer3:"You can define a function using the 'let' keyword."}},{id:317804956238,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Functions and Scope",question:"What is the purpose of parameters in a function?",answers:{answer:"Parameters allow you to pass values into a function to make it more dynamic and reusable.",fakeAnswer1:"Parameters are used to declare variables in a function.",fakeAnswer2:"Parameters are used to define functions in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer3:"Parameters are used to create arrays in a function."}},{id:924178356902,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Functions and Scope",question:"What is a return statement in a function?",answers:{answer:"A return statement specifies the value that a function should return when it's called.",fakeAnswer1:"A return statement is used to define functions in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer2:"A return statement is used to create arrays in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer3:"A return statement is used to declare variables in a function."}},{id:471963825704,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Functions and Scope",question:"What is a global variable in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"A global variable is a variable declared outside of any function and can be accessed from anywhere in the code.",fakeAnswer1:"A global variable is a variable declared inside a function.",fakeAnswer2:"A global variable is a variable declared with the 'let' keyword.",fakeAnswer3:"A global variable is a variable declared with the 'const' keyword."}},{id:758421936507,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Arrays and Array Methods",question:"What is an array in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"An array is a special variable that can hold multiple values under a single name.",fakeAnswer1:"An array is a function in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer2:"An array is an object in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer3:"An array is a string in JavaScript."}},{id:263471985206,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Arrays and Array Methods",question:"How do you access the first element of an array?",answers:{answer:"You can access the first element of an array using index 0 (e.g., array[0]).",fakeAnswer1:"You can access the first element of an array using index 1.",fakeAnswer2:"You can access the first element of an array using the 'first' keyword.",fakeAnswer3:"You can access the first element of an array using the 'start' keyword."}},{id:820146739581,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Arrays and Array Methods",question:"What is the 'length' property of an array?",answers:{answer:"The 'length' property returns the number of elements in an array.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'length' property returns the last element of an array.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'length' property returns the first element of an array.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'length' property returns the sum of all elements in an array."}},{id:507839614872,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Arrays and Array Methods",question:"What is the 'push()' method used for in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"The 'push()' method is used to add one or more elements to the end of an array.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'push()' method is used to remove elements from an array.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'push()' method is used to reverse the order of elements in an array.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'push()' method is used to declare variables in JavaScript."}},{id:914672853019,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Arrays and Array Methods",question:"What is the 'pop()' method used for in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"The 'pop()' method is used to remove and return the last element of an array.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'pop()' method is used to add elements to the end of an array.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'pop()' method is used to create a new array.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'pop()' method is used to declare variables in JavaScript."}},{id:369581247603,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Arrays and Array Methods",question:"What is the 'shift()' method used for in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"The 'shift()' method is used to remove and return the first element of an array.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'shift()' method is used to add elements to the end of an array.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'shift()' method is used to create a new array.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'shift()' method is used to declare variables in JavaScript."}},{id:581962347089,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Arrays and Array Methods",question:"What is the 'unshift()' method used for in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"The 'unshift()' method is used to add one or more elements to the beginning of an array.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'unshift()' method is used to remove elements from an array.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'unshift()' method is used to reverse the order of elements in an array.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'unshift()' method is used to declare variables in JavaScript."}},{id:507836219734,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Arrays and Array Methods",question:"What is the 'splice()' method used for in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"The 'splice()' method is used to add or remove elements from an array at a specified index.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'splice()' method is used to create a new array.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'splice()' method is used to reverse the order of elements in an array.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'splice()' method is used to declare variables in JavaScript."}},{id:193468205712,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Objects and Object Methods",question:"What is an object in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"An object is a collection of key-value pairs used to store and organize data.",fakeAnswer1:"An object is a function in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer2:"An object is a variable in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer3:"An object is a data type in JavaScript."}},{id:678591204367,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Objects and Object Methods",question:"How do you access the value of a property in an object?",answers:{answer:"You can access the value of a property using the dot notation (e.g., object.property) or bracket notation (e.g., object['property']).",fakeAnswer1:"You can access the value of a property using the 'value' keyword.",fakeAnswer2:"You can access the value of a property using the 'get' keyword.",fakeAnswer3:"You can access the value of a property using the 'data' keyword."}},{id:420857361924,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Objects and Object Methods",question:"What is a method in an object?",answers:{answer:"A method in an object is a function that is a property of the object.",fakeAnswer1:"A method in an object is a variable.",fakeAnswer2:"A method in an object is an array.",fakeAnswer3:"A method in an object is an object."}},{id:951267348210,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Objects and Object Methods",question:"How do you add a new property to an object?",answers:{answer:"You can add a new property to an object by simply assigning a value to a new key.",fakeAnswer1:"You can add a new property to an object using the 'add' keyword.",fakeAnswer2:"You can add a new property to an object using the 'create' keyword.",fakeAnswer3:"You can add a new property to an object using the 'property' keyword."}},{id:246380175943,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Objects and Object Methods",question:"What is the 'delete' operator used for in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"The 'delete' operator is used to remove a property from an object.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'delete' operator is used to create a property in an object.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'delete' operator is used to change the value of a property in an object.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'delete' operator is used to declare variables in JavaScript."}},{id:578314962307,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Functions and Scope",question:"What is a callback function in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"A callback function is a function that is passed as an argument to another function and is executed after the completion of that function.",fakeAnswer1:"A callback function is a variable in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer2:"A callback function is an array in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer3:"A callback function is a data type in JavaScript."}},{id:983617245061,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Functions and Scope",question:"What is a closure in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"A closure is a function that has access to its own scope, the outer function's scope, and the global scope.",fakeAnswer1:"A closure is a variable in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer2:"A closure is an object in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer3:"A closure is a data type in JavaScript."}},{id:719582634017,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Functions and Scope",question:"What is the 'this' keyword used for in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"The 'this' keyword refers to the current object in a function or method.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'this' keyword refers to the global object in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'this' keyword refers to a specific value in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'this' keyword refers to a variable in JavaScript."}},{id:614207598361,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Functions and Scope",question:"What is function scope in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"Function scope refers to the visibility and accessibility of variables within a function.",fakeAnswer1:"Function scope refers to the visibility of variables in the global scope.",fakeAnswer2:"Function scope refers to the visibility of variables in an object.",fakeAnswer3:"Function scope refers to the visibility of variables in an array."}},{id:302461978564,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Arrays and Array Methods",question:"What is the 'forEach()' method used for in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"The 'forEach()' method is used to iterate over the elements of an array and perform a specified action for each element.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'forEach()' method is used to add elements to an array.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'forEach()' method is used to remove elements from an array.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'forEach()' method is used to create a new array."}},{id:876935124870,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Arrays and Array Methods",question:"What is the difference between 'map()' and 'forEach()' methods?",answers:{answer:"The 'map()' method creates a new array with the results of calling a provided function on every element in the array, while the 'forEach()' method does not create a new array but instead performs a specified action on each element.",fakeAnswer1:"There is no difference between 'map()' and 'forEach()' methods.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'map()' method returns a new array, while 'forEach()' returns the original array.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'map()' method only works on even-indexed elements."}},{id:461903872516,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Arrays and Array Methods",question:"What is the 'filter()' method used for in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"The 'filter()' method creates a new array with all elements that pass the test implemented by the provided function.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'filter()' method removes all elements from the array.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'filter()' method sorts the array in descending order.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'filter()' method converts the array to a string."}},{id:518429367105,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Arrays and Array Methods",question:"How do you find the index of a specific element in an array?",answers:{answer:"You can use the 'indexOf()' method to find the index of a specific element in an array. It returns -1 if the element is not found.",fakeAnswer1:"You can use the 'includes()' method to find the index of a specific element.",fakeAnswer2:"You can use the 'find()' method to find the index of a specific element.",fakeAnswer3:"You can use the 'search()' method to find the index of a specific element."}},{id:725163498072,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Arrays and Array Methods",question:"What does the 'some()' method do?",answers:{answer:"The 'some()' method checks if at least one element in the array satisfies the provided testing function. It returns true if any element passes the test; otherwise, it returns false.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'some()' method returns true only if all elements pass the test.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'some()' method returns false for all elements.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'some()' method removes all elements from the array."}},{id:349871526304,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Arrays and Array Methods",question:"What is the purpose of the 'reduce()' method?",answers:{answer:"The 'reduce()' method applies a function against an accumulator and each element in the array (from left to right) to reduce it to a single value.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'reduce()' method removes all elements from the array.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'reduce()' method sorts the array in ascending order.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'reduce()' method converts the array to a string."}},{id:610982475361,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Arrays and Array Methods",question:"What is the purpose of the 'reverse()' method?",answers:{answer:"The 'reverse()' method reverses the order of the elements in an array.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'reverse()' method sorts the array in ascending order.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'reverse()' method removes all elements from the array.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'reverse()' method converts the array to a string."}},{id:198345762301,category:"JavaScript",topic:"Arrays and Array Methods",question:"How do you add multiple elements to the beginning of an array?",answers:{answer:"You can use the 'unshift()' method to add one or more elements to the beginning of an array.",fakeAnswer1:"You can use the 'push()' method to add elements to the beginning of an array.",fakeAnswer2:"You can use the 'splice()' method to add elements to the beginning of an array.",fakeAnswer3:"You can use the 'shift()' method to add elements to the beginning of an array."}},{id:731846925073,category:"JavaScript",topic:"JavaScript Basics",question:"What is the purpose of the 'alert()' function?",answers:{answer:"The 'alert()' function displays a dialog box with a specified message and an OK button.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'alert()' function is used to define variables in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'alert()' function is used to create arrays in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'alert()' function is used to add elements to an array."}},{id:362198754016,category:"JavaScript",topic:"JavaScript Basics",question:"What is the purpose of the 'prompt()' function?",answers:{answer:"The 'prompt()' function displays a dialog box that prompts the user for input and returns the entered value as a string.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'prompt()' function is used to remove elements from an array.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'prompt()' function is used to create arrays in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'prompt()' function is used to define variables in JavaScript."}},{id:947612385064,category:"JavaScript",topic:"JavaScript Basics",question:"What is the purpose of the 'confirm()' function?",answers:{answer:"The 'confirm()' function displays a dialog box with a specified message and OK/Cancel buttons. It returns true if the user clicks OK and false if the user clicks Cancel.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'confirm()' function is used to declare variables in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'confirm()' function is used to create arrays in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'confirm()' function is used to add elements to an array."}},{id:513847269041,category:"JavaScript",topic:"JavaScript Basics",question:"What is a comment in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"A comment is a piece of text that is not executed as code. It is used to add notes and explanations to the code.",fakeAnswer1:"A comment is a variable in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer2:"A comment is a function in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer3:"A comment is an array in JavaScript."}},{id:385614972306,category:"JavaScript",topic:"JavaScript Basics",question:"How do you write a single-line comment in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"You can write a single-line comment in JavaScript by using two forward slashes (//) followed by the comment text.",fakeAnswer1:"You can write a single-line comment in JavaScript by using a pair of curly braces ({}).",fakeAnswer2:"You can write a single-line comment in JavaScript by using the 'comment' keyword.",fakeAnswer3:"You can write a single-line comment in JavaScript by using the 'note' keyword."}},{id:971264830412,category:"JavaScript",topic:"JavaScript Basics",question:"How do you write a multi-line comment in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"You can write a multi-line comment in JavaScript by using /* to start the comment and */ to end it. Everything between these symbols is treated as a comment.",fakeAnswer1:"You can write a multi-line comment in JavaScript by using // on each line of the comment.",fakeAnswer2:"You can write a multi-line comment in JavaScript by using a pair of square brackets ([]).",fakeAnswer3:"You can write a multi-line comment in JavaScript by using the 'comment' keyword."}},{id:208135679412,category:"React",topic:"React Basics",question:"What is React?",answers:{answer:"React is a JavaScript library for building user interfaces.",fakeAnswer1:"React is a programming language.",fakeAnswer2:"React is a database management system.",fakeAnswer3:"React is a type of coffee."}},{id:703812964521,category:"React",topic:"React Basics",question:"What is JSX?",answers:{answer:"JSX is a syntax extension for JavaScript recommended for use with React. It allows you to write HTML-like code in your JavaScript files.",fakeAnswer1:"JSX is a JavaScript framework.",fakeAnswer2:"JSX is a type of coffee.",fakeAnswer3:"JSX is a programming language."}},{id:621498735208,category:"React",topic:"React Basics",question:"What is a component in React?",answers:{answer:"A component in React is a reusable, self-contained building block for creating user interfaces.",fakeAnswer1:"A component in React is a type of coffee.",fakeAnswer2:"A component in React is a database management system.",fakeAnswer3:"A component in React is a programming language."}},{id:814269703812,category:"React",topic:"React Basics",question:"What is the virtual DOM in React?",answers:{answer:"The virtual DOM is a lightweight copy of the real DOM that React uses to optimize updates and improve performance.",fakeAnswer1:"The virtual DOM is a programming language.",fakeAnswer2:"The virtual DOM is a type of coffee.",fakeAnswer3:"The virtual DOM is a database management system."}},{id:935714826190,category:"React",topic:"React Basics",question:"What is a prop in React?",answers:{answer:"A prop is a way to pass data from a parent component to a child component in React.",fakeAnswer1:"A prop is a programming language.",fakeAnswer2:"A prop is a type of coffee.",fakeAnswer3:"A prop is a database management system."}},{id:286190473518,category:"React",topic:"Components and Props",question:"How do you define a functional component in React?",answers:{answer:"A functional component in React is defined as a JavaScript function that returns JSX.",fakeAnswer1:"A functional component is defined as an HTML element.",fakeAnswer2:"A functional component is defined as a database management system.",fakeAnswer3:"A functional component is defined as a type of coffee."}},{id:190473518286,category:"React",topic:"Components and Props",question:"What are props in React?",answers:{answer:"Props (short for properties) are a mechanism for passing data from a parent component to a child component in React.",fakeAnswer1:"Props are a type of coffee.",fakeAnswer2:"Props are a programming language.",fakeAnswer3:"Props are a database management system."}},{id:351828619047,category:"React",topic:"Components and Props",question:"What is the purpose of the 'key' prop when rendering lists in React?",answers:{answer:"The 'key' prop is used to give a unique identity to each element in a list of React components. It helps React identify which items have changed, been added, or been removed.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'key' prop is used to define the color of elements in a list.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'key' prop is used to create a new component in React.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'key' prop is used to add styles to elements in a list."}},{id:826190473518,category:"React",topic:"Components and Props",question:"What is the main difference between props and state in React?",answers:{answer:"Props are read-only and are used to pass data from parent to child components, while state is mutable and is used to manage data that can change over time within a component.",fakeAnswer1:"Props are used for styling, while state is used for functionality.",fakeAnswer2:"Props are used to manage component behavior, while state is used for passing data.",fakeAnswer3:"Props and state are the same in React."}},{id:473518286190,category:"React",topic:"State and Lifecycle",question:"What is the 'state' in a React component?",answers:{answer:"The 'state' in a React component is an object that represents the mutable data that can change over time and affects the component's behavior and rendering.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'state' in a React component is a type of coffee.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'state' in a React component is a database management system.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'state' in a React component is a programming language."}},{id:518286190473,category:"React",topic:"State and Lifecycle",question:"How do you update the 'state' in a React component?",answers:{answer:"You can update the 'state' in a React component by calling the 'setState()' method or using hooks like 'useState()' in functional components.",fakeAnswer1:"You can update the 'state' by directly modifying the 'state' object.",fakeAnswer2:"You can update the 'state' by deleting the 'state' object.",fakeAnswer3:"You can update the 'state' by creating a new component."}},{id:286190473518,category:"React",topic:"State and Lifecycle",question:"What is a 'lifecycle' in a React component?",answers:{answer:"The 'lifecycle' of a React component refers to the various stages a component goes through, from initialization to rendering to unmounting. It allows you to hook into specific moments in a component's life and perform actions.",fakeAnswer1:"A 'lifecycle' in React refers to the number of times a component is rendered.",fakeAnswer2:"A 'lifecycle' in React refers to the size of a component.",fakeAnswer3:"A 'lifecycle' in React refers to the color of a component."}},{id:190473518286,category:"React",topic:"State and Lifecycle",question:"What is the 'componentDidMount()' method in React?",answers:{answer:"The 'componentDidMount()' method is a lifecycle method in React that is called after a component has been inserted into the DOM. It is often used for tasks like data fetching and DOM manipulation.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'componentDidMount()' method is used to define component styles.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'componentDidMount()' method is used to delete a component.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'componentDidMount()' method is used to create a component."}},{id:351828619047,category:"React",topic:"Handling Events",question:"How do you handle events in React?",answers:{answer:"In React, you can handle events by using JSX event attributes like 'onClick' and providing a function that will be executed when the event occurs.",fakeAnswer1:"In React, events are handled automatically and do not require any specific syntax.",fakeAnswer2:"In React, you can handle events by using HTML event attributes like 'onmouseover' and 'onmouseout'.",fakeAnswer3:"In React, you can handle events by using the 'event' keyword."}},{id:826190473518,category:"React",topic:"Handling Events",question:"What is 'event delegation' in React?",answers:{answer:"Event delegation in React is a technique where you attach a single event listener to a common ancestor of multiple elements. This allows you to handle events for multiple elements with a single function.",fakeAnswer1:"Event delegation in React is a way to delete events.",fakeAnswer2:"Event delegation in React is a way to create events.",fakeAnswer3:"Event delegation in React is a way to style elements."}},{id:473518286190,category:"React",topic:"Handling Events",question:"What is 'synthetic event' in React?",answers:{answer:"A synthetic event in React is a cross-browser wrapper around the browser's native event. It provides a consistent interface for working with events and handles browser compatibility issues.",fakeAnswer1:"A synthetic event in React is a virtual event that doesn't have any real-world impact.",fakeAnswer2:"A synthetic event in React is an event that is automatically triggered by React components.",fakeAnswer3:"A synthetic event in React is a type of coffee."}},{id:518286190473,category:"React",topic:"Conditional Rendering",question:"How do you conditionally render elements in React?",answers:{answer:"You can conditionally render elements in React by using conditional statements like 'if' or the ternary operator within your JSX code.",fakeAnswer1:"You can conditionally render elements in React by using only 'else' statements.",fakeAnswer2:"You can conditionally render elements in React by using 'switch' statements.",fakeAnswer3:"You can conditionally render elements in React by using 'for' loops."}},{id:286190473518,category:"React",topic:"Conditional Rendering",question:"What is the purpose of the '&&' operator in React conditional rendering?",answers:{answer:"The '&&' operator in React conditional rendering is used to conditionally render an element based on a certain condition. If the condition is true, the element is rendered; otherwise, it is not.",fakeAnswer1:"The '&&' operator in React is used for mathematical calculations.",fakeAnswer2:"The '&&' operator in React is used for defining styles.",fakeAnswer3:"The '&&' operator in React is used for creating components."}},{id:190473518286,category:"React",topic:"Lists and Keys",question:"Why do you need keys when rendering lists in React?",answers:{answer:"Keys in React are used to give a unique identity to each element in a list of components. They help React identify which items have changed, been added, or been removed when updating a list.",fakeAnswer1:"Keys in React are used to define the color of list elements.",fakeAnswer2:"Keys in React are used to create new components in a list.",fakeAnswer3:"Keys in React are used to add styles to list elements."}},{id:351828619047,category:"React",topic:"Lists and Keys",question:"What happens if you don't provide keys when rendering lists in React?",answers:{answer:"If you don't provide keys when rendering lists in React, React may have difficulties efficiently updating the list and may not be able to distinguish between different list items, leading to unexpected behavior.",fakeAnswer1:"If you don't provide keys, React will automatically generate keys for list items.",fakeAnswer2:"If you don't provide keys, React will display an error message.",fakeAnswer3:"If you don't provide keys, React will automatically remove list items."}},{id:826190473518,category:"React",topic:"Lists and Keys",question:"What is the purpose of the 'map()' method in React when rendering lists?",answers:{answer:"The 'map()' method in React is used to iterate over an array and create a new array of React components based on the original data. It is often used for rendering dynamic lists of components.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'map()' method in React is used for sorting arrays.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'map()' method in React is used for filtering arrays.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'map()' method in React is used for deleting elements from arrays."}},{id:473518286190,category:"React",topic:"Forms and Controlled Components",question:"What is a controlled component in React forms?",answers:{answer:"A controlled component in React forms is a form element whose value is controlled by the component's state. Changes to the input value are handled through state, making it easy to access and manipulate form data.",fakeAnswer1:"A controlled component in React forms is a form element that does not use state.",fakeAnswer2:"A controlled component in React forms is a form element that uses a database.",fakeAnswer3:"A controlled component in React forms is a form element that is not part of the DOM."}},{id:518286190473,category:"React",topic:"Forms and Controlled Components",question:"What is the 'value' prop used for in controlled input elements in React forms?",answers:{answer:"The 'value' prop in controlled input elements is used to set the current value of the input element. It is controlled by the component's state, allowing you to manage and update the input value.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'value' prop in controlled input elements is used for styling purposes.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'value' prop in controlled input elements is used for defining event handlers.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'value' prop in controlled input elements is used to create new components."}},{id:286190473518,category:"React",topic:"Forms and Controlled Components",question:"What is the purpose of the 'onChange' event handler in controlled input elements in React forms?",answers:{answer:"The 'onChange' event handler in controlled input elements is used to detect and handle changes to the input value. When the user types or selects something in the input field, the 'onChange' event is triggered, allowing you to update the component's state.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'onChange' event handler is used to submit a form.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'onChange' event handler is used to delete a form.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'onChange' event handler is used to style a form."}},{id:190473518286,category:"React",topic:"Component Composition",question:"What is component composition in React?",answers:{answer:"Component composition in React is the practice of building complex user interfaces by combining and reusing smaller, self-contained components. It allows for a more modular and maintainable codebase.",fakeAnswer1:"Component composition in React is the process of deleting components.",fakeAnswer2:"Component composition in React is the process of creating a single large component for the entire application.",fakeAnswer3:"Component composition in React is the process of defining styles."}},{id:351828619047,category:"React",topic:"Component Composition",question:"What are the benefits of component composition in React?",answers:{answer:"The benefits of component composition in React include code reusability, maintainability, and the ability to break complex UIs into smaller, manageable parts. It also promotes a more declarative and modular coding style.",fakeAnswer1:"The benefits of component composition in React include faster performance.",fakeAnswer2:"The benefits of component composition in React include automatic styling.",fakeAnswer3:"The benefits of component composition in React include database management."}},{id:826190473518,category:"React",topic:"Hooks",question:"What are React hooks?",answers:{answer:"React hooks are functions that allow you to use state and other React features in functional components. They provide a way to reuse stateful logic without changing your component hierarchy.",fakeAnswer1:"React hooks are tools used for building navigation menus.",fakeAnswer2:"React hooks are used for defining styles in React components.",fakeAnswer3:"React hooks are a type of coffee."}},{id:473518286190,category:"React",topic:"Hooks",question:"What is the 'useState' hook used for in React?",answers:{answer:"The 'useState' hook in React is used to add state management to functional components. It allows you to declare and update state variables.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'useState' hook is used for styling purposes.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'useState' hook is used to create new components.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'useState' hook is used for deleting components."}},{id:518286190473,category:"React",topic:"Hooks",question:"What is the 'useEffect' hook used for in React?",answers:{answer:"The 'useEffect' hook in React is used for performing side effects in functional components. It allows you to manage tasks like data fetching, DOM manipulation, and subscriptions.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'useEffect' hook is used to define component styles.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'useEffect' hook is used to delete components.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'useEffect' hook is used to create components."}},{id:286190473518,category:"React",topic:"React Router",question:"What is React Router?",answers:{answer:"React Router is a popular library for adding routing and navigation to React applications. It allows you to create single-page applications with multiple views and URLs.",fakeAnswer1:"React Router is a database management system.",fakeAnswer2:"React Router is a type of coffee.",fakeAnswer3:"React Router is a state management library."}},{id:190473518286,category:"React",topic:"React Router",question:"How do you declare a route in React Router?",answers:{answer:"In React Router, you declare routes using the 'Route' component. You specify the path and the component to render when that path matches the URL.",fakeAnswer1:"In React Router, routes are declared using the 'Router' component.",fakeAnswer2:"In React Router, routes are declared using HTML tags.",fakeAnswer3:"In React Router, routes are declared using JavaScript functions."}},{id:21,category:"NodeJS",topic:"CoreModules",question:"What is the purpose of the 'fs' module in Node.js?",answers:{answer:"The 'fs' module in Node.js is used for working with the file system. It provides functions for creating, reading, updating, and deleting files and directories.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'fs' module is used for creating web servers in Node.js.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'fs' module is used for handling database operations in Node.js.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'fs' module is used for working with frontend components in Node.js."}},{id:826190473518,category:"React",topic:"React Router",question:"What is the purpose of the 'Link' component in React Router?",answers:{answer:"The 'Link' component in React Router is used to navigate between different views or pages in a React application. It prevents the browser from doing a full page refresh and provides a smooth client-side navigation experience.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'Link' component is used to create hyperlinks to external websites.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'Link' component is used for styling purposes in React Router.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'Link' component is used for database queries in React Router."}},{id:473518286190,category:"React",topic:"React Router",question:"What is a 'Route Parameter' in React Router?",answers:{answer:"A 'Route Parameter' in React Router is a dynamic segment of a URL path that can be accessed and used in a React component. It allows you to create flexible and dynamic routes.",fakeAnswer1:"A 'Route Parameter' is a predefined constant in React Router.",fakeAnswer2:"A 'Route Parameter' is a way to define styles in React Router.",fakeAnswer3:"A 'Route Parameter' is a data structure in React Router."}},{id:518286190473,category:"React",topic:"React Router",question:"What is the 'Switch' component used for in React Router?",answers:{answer:"The 'Switch' component in React Router is used to render only the first 'Route' or 'Redirect' that matches the current location. It helps ensure that only one route is rendered at a time.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'Switch' component is used to toggle between light and dark mode in React Router.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'Switch' component is used to create animations in React Router.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'Switch' component is used to delete routes in React Router."}},{id:286190473518,category:"React",topic:"Hooks",question:"What is the 'useContext' hook used for in React?",answers:{answer:"The 'useContext' hook in React is used for accessing context values and providing them to components. It allows you to access shared data without passing props through the component tree.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'useContext' hook is used for defining component styles.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'useContext' hook is used for deleting components.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'useContext' hook is used for creating components."}},{id:190473518286,category:"React",topic:"Hooks",question:"What is the 'useReducer' hook used for in React?",answers:{answer:"The 'useReducer' hook in React is used for managing complex state logic in functional components. It is often used when the state transitions depend on the previous state.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'useReducer' hook is used to create animations in React.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'useReducer' hook is used for defining component styles.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'useReducer' hook is used to create components."}},{id:351828619047,category:"React",topic:"Hooks",question:"What is the 'useMemo' hook used for in React?",answers:{answer:"The 'useMemo' hook in React is used for memoizing expensive calculations and preventing unnecessary re-renders. It allows you to optimize the performance of your components.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'useMemo' hook is used to define component styles.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'useMemo' hook is used to create animations in React.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'useMemo' hook is used to delete components."}},{id:826190473518,category:"React",topic:"Hooks",question:"What is the 'useCallback' hook used for in React?",answers:{answer:"The 'useCallback' hook in React is used for memoizing callback functions to prevent unnecessary re-creation of functions during re-renders. It is often used to optimize performance in child components.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'useCallback' hook is used to define component styles.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'useCallback' hook is used for creating components.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'useCallback' hook is used for deleting components."}},{id:473518286190,category:"React",topic:"React Router",question:"How do you pass parameters to a route in React Router?",answers:{answer:"You can pass parameters to a route in React Router by including them in the route's path using the colon syntax, like ':parameterName'. These parameters can then be accessed in the component via the 'useParams' hook.",fakeAnswer1:"You can pass parameters to a route in React Router using the 'params' prop.",fakeAnswer2:"You can pass parameters to a route in React Router using the 'query' string.",fakeAnswer3:"You can pass parameters to a route in React Router using a separate JavaScript file."}},{id:518286190473,category:"React",topic:"React Router",question:"What is the purpose of the 'useHistory' hook in React Router?",answers:{answer:"The 'useHistory' hook in React Router is used to manage the navigation history. It provides methods for programmatically navigating to different routes and accessing the current location.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'useHistory' hook is used to define component styles.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'useHistory' hook is used for creating components.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'useHistory' hook is used for deleting components."}},{id:286190473518,category:"React",topic:"React Router",question:"What is the purpose of the 'useLocation' hook in React Router?",answers:{answer:"The 'useLocation' hook in React Router is used to access the current location object, which contains information about the current URL and its properties. It allows you to read and interact with the URL.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'useLocation' hook is used to define component styles.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'useLocation' hook is used to create animations in React Router.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'useLocation' hook is used for deleting components."}},{id:190473518286,category:"React",topic:"React Router",question:"What is the purpose of the 'useRouteMatch' hook in React Router?",answers:{answer:"The 'useRouteMatch' hook in React Router is used to match the current URL against a specified path or pattern. It returns information about the matching route, such as URL parameters and the matched path.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'useRouteMatch' hook is used to define component styles.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'useRouteMatch' hook is used to create animations in React Router.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'useRouteMatch' hook is used for deleting components."}},{id:22,category:"NodeJS",topic:"CoreModules",question:"What is the purpose of the 'http' module in Node.js?",answers:{answer:"The 'http' module in Node.js is used for creating HTTP servers and making HTTP requests. It allows you to handle HTTP requests and responses.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'http' module is used for handling file operations in Node.js.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'http' module is used for working with databases in Node.js.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'http' module is used for rendering web pages in Node.js."}},{id:23,category:"NodeJS",topic:"CoreModules",question:"What is the purpose of the 'path' module in Node.js?",answers:{answer:"The 'path' module in Node.js is used for working with file paths and directories. It provides functions for manipulating and resolving file paths.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'path' module is used for handling HTTP requests in Node.js.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'path' module is used for creating web components in Node.js.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'path' module is used for rendering web pages in Node.js."}},{id:24,category:"NodeJS",topic:"CoreModules",question:"What is the purpose of the 'util' module in Node.js?",answers:{answer:"The 'util' module in Node.js provides utility functions that can be used for various purposes, such as debugging, error handling, and working with objects.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'util' module is used for handling file operations in Node.js.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'util' module is used for creating web servers in Node.js.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'util' module is used for rendering web pages in Node.js."}},{id:25,category:"NodeJS",topic:"CoreModules",question:"What is the purpose of the 'events' module in Node.js?",answers:{answer:"The 'events' module in Node.js allows you to create and emit custom events. It is used for implementing the EventEmitter pattern.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'events' module is used for handling HTTP requests in Node.js.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'events' module is used for working with databases in Node.js.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'events' module is used for rendering web pages in Node.js."}},{id:26,category:"NodeJS",topic:"CoreModules",question:"What is the purpose of the 'os' module in Node.js?",answers:{answer:"The 'os' module in Node.js provides information about the operating system on which Node.js is running. It allows you to access information like CPU architecture, memory, and network interfaces.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'os' module is used for creating web servers in Node.js.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'os' module is used for handling file operations in Node.js.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'os' module is used for rendering web pages in Node.js."}},{id:27,category:"NodeJS",topic:"CoreModules",question:"What is the purpose of the 'child_process' module in Node.js?",answers:{answer:"The 'child_process' module in Node.js allows you to create and interact with child processes. It is used for running external commands and scripts from within a Node.js application.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'child_process' module is used for handling HTTP requests in Node.js.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'child_process' module is used for working with databases in Node.js.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'child_process' module is used for rendering web pages in Node.js."}},{id:28,category:"NodeJS",topic:"CoreModules",question:"What is the purpose of the 'crypto' module in Node.js?",answers:{answer:"The 'crypto' module in Node.js provides cryptographic functionality. It allows you to perform tasks like creating hashes, encrypting and decrypting data, and generating secure random numbers.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'crypto' module is used for handling file operations in Node.js.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'crypto' module is used for creating web servers in Node.js.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'crypto' module is used for rendering web pages in Node.js."}},{id:29,category:"NodeJS",topic:"CoreModules",question:"What is the purpose of the 'buffer' module in Node.js?",answers:{answer:"The 'buffer' module in Node.js is used for working with binary data. It allows you to create, manipulate, and read binary data directly.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'buffer' module is used for handling HTTP requests in Node.js.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'buffer' module is used for working with databases in Node.js.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'buffer' module is used for rendering web pages in Node.js."}},{id:30,category:"NodeJS",topic:"CoreModules",question:"What is the purpose of the 'url' module in Node.js?",answers:{answer:"The 'url' module in Node.js provides utilities for parsing and formatting URLs. It allows you to work with URLs in a structured way.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'url' module is used for creating web servers in Node.js.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'url' module is used for handling file operations in Node.js.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'url' module is used for rendering web pages in Node.js."}},{id:31,category:"MongoDB",topic:"QueryingDocuments",question:"What is a MongoDB query?",answers:{answer:"A MongoDB query is a request for data from a MongoDB database. It specifies the criteria for selecting documents from a collection.",fakeAnswer1:"A MongoDB query is a type of data storage in MongoDB.",fakeAnswer2:"A MongoDB query is used to create new databases in MongoDB.",fakeAnswer3:"A MongoDB query is a way to define schema for MongoDB collections."}},{id:32,category:"MongoDB",topic:"QueryingDocuments",question:"What is the purpose of the 'find' method in MongoDB?",answers:{answer:"The 'find' method in MongoDB is used to query documents in a collection based on specified criteria. It returns a cursor that can be used to iterate over the matching documents.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'find' method is used to insert documents into a collection in MongoDB.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'find' method is used to update documents in a collection in MongoDB.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'find' method is used to delete documents from a collection in MongoDB."}},{id:33,category:"MongoDB",topic:"QueryingDocuments",question:"What is the purpose of the 'findOne' method in MongoDB?",answers:{answer:"The 'findOne' method in MongoDB is used to query and retrieve a single document from a collection based on specified criteria. It returns the first matching document or null if no match is found.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'findOne' method is used to query all documents in a collection in MongoDB.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'findOne' method is used to update documents in a collection in MongoDB.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'findOne' method is used to delete documents from a collection in MongoDB."}},{id:34,category:"MongoDB",topic:"QueryingDocuments",question:"What is the purpose of the 'count' method in MongoDB?",answers:{answer:"The 'count' method in MongoDB is used to count the number of documents in a collection that match a specified query criteria.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'count' method is used to insert documents into a collection in MongoDB.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'count' method is used to update documents in a collection in MongoDB.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'count' method is used to delete documents from a collection in MongoDB."}},{id:35,category:"MongoDB",topic:"QueryingDocuments",question:"What is the purpose of the 'sort' method in MongoDB?",answers:{answer:"The 'sort' method in MongoDB is used to sort the results of a query in ascending or descending order based on one or more fields in the documents.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'sort' method is used to insert documents into a collection in MongoDB.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'sort' method is used to update documents in a collection in MongoDB.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'sort' method is used to delete documents from a collection in MongoDB."}},{id:36,category:"MongoDB",topic:"QueryingDocuments",question:"What is the purpose of the 'limit' method in MongoDB?",answers:{answer:"The 'limit' method in MongoDB is used to limit the number of documents returned by a query. It specifies a maximum number of documents to return.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'limit' method is used to insert documents into a collection in MongoDB.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'limit' method is used to update documents in a collection in MongoDB.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'limit' method is used to delete documents from a collection in MongoDB."}},{id:37,category:"MongoDB",topic:"QueryingDocuments",question:"What is the purpose of the 'skip' method in MongoDB?",answers:{answer:"The 'skip' method in MongoDB is used to skip a specified number of documents in the result set of a query. It is often used for pagination.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'skip' method is used to insert documents into a collection in MongoDB.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'skip' method is used to update documents in a collection in MongoDB.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'skip' method is used to delete documents from a collection in MongoDB."}},{id:38,category:"MongoDB",topic:"QueryingDocuments",question:"What is the purpose of the 'aggregate' method in MongoDB?",answers:{answer:"The 'aggregate' method in MongoDB is used to perform complex operations on data in a collection. It allows you to apply multiple stages of transformations to the data.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'aggregate' method is used to insert documents into a collection in MongoDB.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'aggregate' method is used to update documents in a collection in MongoDB.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'aggregate' method is used to delete documents from a collection in MongoDB."}},{id:39,category:"MongoDB",topic:"QueryingDocuments",question:"What is the purpose of the 'distinct' method in MongoDB?",answers:{answer:"The 'distinct' method in MongoDB is used to retrieve the distinct values of a field in a collection. It returns an array of unique values.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'distinct' method is used to insert documents into a collection in MongoDB.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'distinct' method is used to update documents in a collection in MongoDB.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'distinct' method is used to delete documents from a collection in MongoDB."}},{id:40,category:"MongoDB",topic:"QueryingDocuments",question:"What is the purpose of the 'mapReduce' method in MongoDB?",answers:{answer:"The 'mapReduce' method in MongoDB is used for aggregating and processing data in a collection using JavaScript functions. It allows for custom data transformations and analysis.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'mapReduce' method is used to insert documents into a collection in MongoDB.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'mapReduce' method is used to update documents in a collection in MongoDB.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'mapReduce' method is used to delete documents from a collection in MongoDB."}},{id:758291634520,category:"JavaScript",topic:"JavaScript Basics",question:"What is a closure in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"A closure in JavaScript is a function that has access to the variables and scope of its containing or outer function, even after the outer function has finished executing.",fakeAnswer1:"A closure is a built-in JavaScript data type.",fakeAnswer2:"A closure is used to close a web page.",fakeAnswer3:"A closure is a way to create loops in JavaScript."}},{id:643189257420,category:"JavaScript",topic:"JavaScript Basics",question:"What is the difference between 'let', 'const', and 'var' in variable declaration?",answers:{answer:"'let' and 'const' are block-scoped variables, while 'var' is function-scoped. 'let' allows reassignment, 'const' does not.",fakeAnswer1:"'let', 'const', and 'var' are identical in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer2:"'const' allows reassignment, while 'let' does not.",fakeAnswer3:"'var' is block-scoped, while 'let' and 'const' are function-scoped."}},{id:892456013478,category:"JavaScript",topic:"JavaScript Basics",question:"What is the 'this' keyword in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"The 'this' keyword in JavaScript refers to the current execution context, which can vary depending on how a function is called.",fakeAnswer1:"'this' is a reserved keyword in JavaScript that cannot be used in code.",fakeAnswer2:"'this' always refers to the global object in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer3:"'this' is used to define a new variable in JavaScript."}},{id:104732598672,category:"JavaScript",topic:"JavaScript Basics",question:"What are the primitive data types in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"The primitive data types in JavaScript are number, string, boolean, null, undefined, bigint, and symbol.",fakeAnswer1:"The primitive data types in JavaScript are array, object, and function.",fakeAnswer2:"There are no primitive data types in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer3:"The primitive data types in JavaScript are only number and string."}},{id:524698731420,category:"JavaScript",topic:"JavaScript Basics",question:"How do you check if a variable is of type 'function' in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"You can use the 'typeof' operator to check if a variable is of type 'function'. It returns 'function' for functions.",fakeAnswer1:"You can use the 'isFunction()' method to check the type of a variable.",fakeAnswer2:"JavaScript does not provide a way to check the type of a variable.",fakeAnswer3:"You can use the 'isFunction' keyword to check if a variable is a function."}},{id:935267148932,category:"JavaScript",topic:"JavaScript Basics",question:"What is the purpose of the 'parseInt()' function in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"The 'parseInt()' function in JavaScript is used to parse a string and convert it to an integer.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'parseInt()' function is used to find the first occurrence of a string in another string.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'parseInt()' function is used to round a floating-point number to the nearest integer.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'parseInt()' function is used to convert an integer to a string."}},{id:349862571023,category:"JavaScript",topic:"JavaScript Basics",question:"What is a callback function in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"A callback function in JavaScript is a function that is passed as an argument to another function and is executed after the completion of that function.",fakeAnswer1:"A callback function is a function that is defined inside another function.",fakeAnswer2:"A callback function is a function that is called only once in a JavaScript program.",fakeAnswer3:"A callback function is a function that is used for mathematical calculations."}},{id:762104938527,category:"JavaScript",topic:"JavaScript Basics",question:"What is an arrow function in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"An arrow function in JavaScript is a concise way to write functions. It has a shorter syntax compared to traditional function expressions.",fakeAnswer1:"An arrow function is a function that always returns 'undefined'.",fakeAnswer2:"An arrow function is a function that is defined using 'function' keyword.",fakeAnswer3:"An arrow function is a function that can only be used for asynchronous operations."}},{id:624870159346,category:"JavaScript",topic:"JavaScript Basics",question:"What is the 'let' keyword used for in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"The 'let' keyword in JavaScript is used to declare block-scoped variables that can be reassigned.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'let' keyword is used to declare global variables.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'let' keyword is used to declare constants in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'let' keyword is used to define functions in JavaScript."}},{id:820974563812,category:"JavaScript",topic:"JavaScript Basics",question:"What is the purpose of the 'break' statement in JavaScript?",answers:{answer:"The 'break' statement in JavaScript is used to exit a loop prematurely or terminate a switch statement.",fakeAnswer1:"The 'break' statement is used to start a new loop in JavaScript.",fakeAnswer2:"The 'break' statement is used to skip the current iteration of a loop.",fakeAnswer3:"The 'break' statement is used to create a recursive function in JavaScript."}},{id:462318709541,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Schema Basics",question:"What is a Mongoose schema used for?",answers:{answer:"A Mongoose schema is used to define the structure of documents in a MongoDB collection.",fakeAnswer1:"A Mongoose schema is a type of database index.",fakeAnswer2:"A Mongoose schema defines CSS styles for web pages.",fakeAnswer3:"A Mongoose schema is used to send emails."}},{id:812459637021,category:"Mongoose",topic:"CRUD Operations",question:"How do you create a new document in Mongoose?",answers:{answer:"You can create a new document in Mongoose using the `create` method.",fakeAnswer1:"You can create a new document using the `delete` method.",fakeAnswer2:"You can create a new document using the `update` method.",fakeAnswer3:"You can create a new document using the `find` method."}},{id:693178245001,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Validation and Middleware",question:"What is the purpose of middleware in Mongoose?",answers:{answer:"Middleware in Mongoose allows you to execute functions before or after certain database operations, such as saving a document.",fakeAnswer1:"Middleware is used to style HTML elements.",fakeAnswer2:"Middleware is a type of database query.",fakeAnswer3:"Middleware is used to send HTTP requests."}},{id:135702496831,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Queries and Filtering",question:"How do you perform a simple query in Mongoose?",answers:{answer:"You can perform a simple query in Mongoose using the `find` method.",fakeAnswer1:"You can perform a query using the `validate` method.",fakeAnswer2:"You can perform a query using the `update` method.",fakeAnswer3:"You can perform a query using the `create` method."}},{id:950163274481,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Relationships and References",question:"What is a reference in Mongoose?",answers:{answer:"A reference in Mongoose is a way to establish a relationship between documents in different collections by linking them using an identifier.",fakeAnswer1:"A reference is a type of data validation.",fakeAnswer2:"A reference is used to apply styles to HTML elements.",fakeAnswer3:"A reference is used to create new databases."}},{id:217068934510,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Embedded Documents",question:"What are embedded documents in Mongoose?",answers:{answer:"Embedded documents in Mongoose are documents that are nested within other documents, allowing you to store related data in a single document.",fakeAnswer1:"Embedded documents are used for creating forms.",fakeAnswer2:"Embedded documents are used to define CSS styles.",fakeAnswer3:"Embedded documents are used for sending emails."}},{id:579120384617,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Indexes and Performance",question:"Why are indexes important in MongoDB?",answers:{answer:"Indexes in MongoDB improve query performance by allowing the database to quickly locate and retrieve documents based on specific fields.",fakeAnswer1:"Indexes are used for defining database schemas.",fakeAnswer2:"Indexes are used for creating web pages.",fakeAnswer3:"Indexes are used for sorting data."}},{id:386154207981,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Aggregation Framework",question:"What is the MongoDB aggregation framework?",answers:{answer:"The MongoDB aggregation framework is a powerful tool for processing and transforming data within a MongoDB collection, allowing for complex operations like filtering, grouping, and sorting.",fakeAnswer1:"The aggregation framework is a type of data validation.",fakeAnswer2:"The aggregation framework is used for defining HTML structure.",fakeAnswer3:"The aggregation framework is used for sending HTTP requests."}},{id:524718539620,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Transactions and Atomicity",question:"What is the role of transactions in Mongoose?",answers:{answer:"Transactions in Mongoose ensure that a series of database operations are executed as a single, atomic unit, maintaining data consistency and integrity.",fakeAnswer1:"Transactions are used for creating database indexes.",fakeAnswer2:"Transactions are used for defining CSS styles.",fakeAnswer3:"Transactions are used for sending emails."}},{id:673819240516,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Error Handling",question:"How can you handle errors in Mongoose?",answers:{answer:"You can handle errors in Mongoose by using try...catch blocks or by providing error callback functions to database operations.",fakeAnswer1:"Errors in Mongoose are automatically handled by the framework.",fakeAnswer2:"Error handling in Mongoose is used for creating web forms.",fakeAnswer3:"Error handling in Mongoose is used for defining HTML attributes."}},{id:105937284610,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Schema Basics",question:"What is a Mongoose schema type?",answers:{answer:"A Mongoose schema type represents the data type of a field in a schema. It defines the type and validation rules for that field.",fakeAnswer1:"A Mongoose schema type is a JavaScript function.",fakeAnswer2:"A Mongoose schema type defines the structure of an entire document.",fakeAnswer3:"A Mongoose schema type is used for defining HTML styles."}},{id:208145739162,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Schema Basics",question:"How do you define a string field in a Mongoose schema?",answers:{answer:"You can define a string field in a Mongoose schema using the `String` schema type.",fakeAnswer1:"You can define a string field using the `Number` schema type.",fakeAnswer2:"You can define a string field using the `Array` schema type.",fakeAnswer3:"You can define a string field using the `Boolean` schema type."}},{id:674820193581,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Schema Basics",question:"What is the purpose of default values in a Mongoose schema?",answers:{answer:"Default values in a Mongoose schema provide a fallback value for a field if it is not explicitly set during document creation.",fakeAnswer1:"Default values ensure that a field cannot be changed after document creation.",fakeAnswer2:"Default values are used for defining database indexes.",fakeAnswer3:"Default values are used for defining CSS styles."}},{id:119384572610,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Schema Basics",question:"How can you add validation to a Mongoose schema field?",answers:{answer:"You can add validation to a Mongoose schema field by specifying a `validate` option with a validation function.",fakeAnswer1:"Validation is automatically applied to all schema fields in Mongoose.",fakeAnswer2:"Validation is added using the `transform` option in Mongoose.",fakeAnswer3:"Validation is added using the `unique` option in Mongoose."}},{id:405729816324,category:"Mongoose",topic:"CRUD Operations",question:"What is the purpose of the `save` method in Mongoose?",answers:{answer:"The `save` method in Mongoose is used to save a document to the database. It can be called on an existing document to update it or on a new document to create it.",fakeAnswer1:"The `save` method is used to delete documents in Mongoose.",fakeAnswer2:"The `save` method is used to retrieve documents from the database.",fakeAnswer3:"The `save` method is used for creating web pages."}},{id:283916547024,category:"Mongoose",topic:"CRUD Operations",question:"What is the difference between `updateOne` and `updateMany` in Mongoose?",answers:{answer:"The `updateOne` method in Mongoose updates a single document that matches the specified conditions, while `updateMany` updates all documents that match the conditions.",fakeAnswer1:"There is no difference between `updateOne` and `updateMany` in Mongoose.",fakeAnswer2:"The `updateOne` method updates all documents, while `updateMany` updates only one.",fakeAnswer3:"The `updateOne` method deletes documents, while `updateMany` creates new documents."}},{id:937284615029,category:"Mongoose",topic:"CRUD Operations",question:"What is the purpose of the `findByIdAndDelete` method in Mongoose?",answers:{answer:"The `findByIdAndDelete` method in Mongoose finds a document by its ID and removes it from the database.",fakeAnswer1:"The `findByIdAndDelete` method updates a document by its ID.",fakeAnswer2:"The `findByIdAndDelete` method retrieves a document by its ID.",fakeAnswer3:"The `findByIdAndDelete` method is used for creating forms."}},{id:610294853172,category:"Mongoose",topic:"CRUD Operations",question:"How can you sort the results of a Mongoose query in ascending order?",answers:{answer:"You can use the `sort` method with a field name in Mongoose to sort the results of a query in ascending order.",fakeAnswer1:"Mongoose does not support sorting query results.",fakeAnswer2:"You can use the `filter` method to sort results.",fakeAnswer3:"You can use the `limit` method to sort results."}},{id:153627490824,category:"Mongoose",topic:"CRUD Operations",question:"What is the purpose of the `deleteMany` method in Mongoose?",answers:{answer:"The `deleteMany` method in Mongoose deletes all documents that match the specified conditions from the database.",fakeAnswer1:"The `deleteMany` method updates documents that match the conditions.",fakeAnswer2:"The `deleteMany` method retrieves documents that match the conditions.",fakeAnswer3:"The `deleteMany` method is used for defining CSS styles."}},{id:857610294382,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Validation and Middleware",question:"What is a Mongoose middleware?",answers:{answer:"A Mongoose middleware is a function that runs at specified points during the document's lifecycle. It can intercept and modify document operations like saving and removing.",fakeAnswer1:"A Mongoose middleware is a type of database query.",fakeAnswer2:"A Mongoose middleware is used for defining HTML attributes.",fakeAnswer3:"A Mongoose middleware is used for creating web forms."}},{id:749810356284,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Validation and Middleware",question:"When does Mongoose execute `pre` middleware?",answers:{answer:"Mongoose executes `pre` middleware before specific document operations, such as `save`, `validate`, `remove`, and others.",fakeAnswer1:"Mongoose executes `pre` middleware after document operations.",fakeAnswer2:"Mongoose does not support middleware.",fakeAnswer3:"Mongoose executes `pre` middleware before creating forms."}},{id:824509317468,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Validation and Middleware",question:"How can you access the document being processed in a Mongoose middleware function?",answers:{answer:"You can access the document being processed in a Mongoose middleware function using the `this` keyword, which refers to the document.",fakeAnswer1:"You cannot access the document in middleware functions.",fakeAnswer2:"You can access the document using the `find` method.",fakeAnswer3:"You can access the document using the `update` method."}},{id:356284790123,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Validation and Middleware",question:"What is the purpose of the `next` function in Mongoose middleware?",answers:{answer:"The `next` function in Mongoose middleware is used to pass control to the next middleware function in the stack.",fakeAnswer1:"The `next` function is used to cancel the middleware operation.",fakeAnswer2:"The `next` function is used for defining HTML structure.",fakeAnswer3:"The `next` function is used for creating web pages."}},{id:468279013524,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Queries and Filtering",question:"What is a Mongoose query?",answers:{answer:"A Mongoose query is a set of conditions that you can use to retrieve documents from a MongoDB collection. It is constructed using Mongoose methods.",fakeAnswer1:"A Mongoose query is a type of database index.",fakeAnswer2:"A Mongoose query is used to define CSS styles for web pages.",fakeAnswer3:"A Mongoose query is used for sending emails."}},{id:901356284279,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Queries and Filtering",question:"How can you perform a case-insensitive query in Mongoose?",answers:{answer:"You can perform a case-insensitive query in Mongoose by using the `$regex` operator with the `i` flag.",fakeAnswer1:"Mongoose does not support case-insensitive queries.",fakeAnswer2:"You can perform case-insensitive queries using the `limit` method.",fakeAnswer3:"You can perform case-insensitive queries using the `validate` method."}},{id:524687901356,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Queries and Filtering",question:"What is the purpose of the `find` method in Mongoose?",answers:{answer:"The `find` method in Mongoose is used to retrieve documents from a collection that match specified conditions. It returns an array of matching documents.",fakeAnswer1:"The `find` method is used to create new documents.",fakeAnswer2:"The `find` method is used for defining database indexes.",fakeAnswer3:"The `find` method is used to delete documents."}},{id:684279013562,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Queries and Filtering",question:"What is the purpose of the `$and` operator in Mongoose queries?",answers:{answer:"The `$and` operator in Mongoose queries allows you to combine multiple conditions and retrieve documents that satisfy all of them.",fakeAnswer1:"The `$and` operator retrieves documents that satisfy any of the conditions.",fakeAnswer2:"The `$and` operator is used to define CSS styles.",fakeAnswer3:"The `$and` operator is used for creating web forms."}},{id:356290134568,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Relationships and References",question:"What is a one-to-many relationship in Mongoose?",answers:{answer:"A one-to-many relationship in Mongoose refers to a situation where one document in a collection is associated with multiple documents in another collection through references.",fakeAnswer1:"A one-to-many relationship means that one document can only be associated with one document in another collection.",fakeAnswer2:"A one-to-many relationship is used to create web forms.",fakeAnswer3:"A one-to-many relationship is used for defining database indexes."}},{id:901356248279,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Relationships and References",question:"How can you establish a one-to-many relationship in Mongoose?",answers:{answer:"You can establish a one-to-many relationship in Mongoose by using references in the parent document to point to child documents in another collection.",fakeAnswer1:"You can establish a one-to-many relationship using the `delete` method.",fakeAnswer2:"You can establish a one-to-many relationship using the `create` method.",fakeAnswer3:"You can establish a one-to-many relationship using the `find` method."}},{id:456834901356,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Relationships and References",question:"What is the purpose of population in Mongoose?",answers:{answer:"Population in Mongoose is the process of replacing references in a document with the actual documents from another collection, making it easier to work with related data.",fakeAnswer1:"Population is used for creating web pages.",fakeAnswer2:"Population is used for defining database indexes.",fakeAnswer3:"Population is used for sending emails."}},{id:913568467290,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Relationships and References",question:"What is a subdocument in Mongoose?",answers:{answer:"A subdocument in Mongoose is a document that is nested within another document, typically used for representing an embedded one-to-many relationship.",fakeAnswer1:"A subdocument is a separate document in Mongoose.",fakeAnswer2:"A subdocument is used for defining CSS styles.",fakeAnswer3:"A subdocument is used for creating web forms."}},{id:824679013568,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Relationships and References",question:"How can you create and save subdocuments in Mongoose?",answers:{answer:"You can create and save subdocuments in Mongoose by defining them within the parent document schema and using the `push` method to add them to the parent document's array.",fakeAnswer1:"Subdocuments cannot be created and saved in Mongoose.",fakeAnswer2:"Subdocuments are created using the `find` method.",fakeAnswer3:"Subdocuments are created using the `update` method."}},{id:568467901324,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Indexes and Performance",question:"What is the purpose of indexing in Mongoose?",answers:{answer:"Indexing in Mongoose is used to improve the performance of database queries by creating data structures that allow for faster data retrieval.",fakeAnswer1:"Indexing is used to define database schema.",fakeAnswer2:"Indexing is used for creating web pages.",fakeAnswer3:"Indexing is used to define CSS styles."}},{id:901356824679,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Indexes and Performance",question:"How can you create an index on a Mongoose schema field?",answers:{answer:"You can create an index on a Mongoose schema field by using the `index` option when defining the field in the schema.",fakeAnswer1:"Indexes cannot be created on Mongoose schema fields.",fakeAnswer2:"Indexes are created using the `validate` method.",fakeAnswer3:"Indexes are created using the `delete` method."}},{id:679013568124,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Indexes and Performance",question:"What is the purpose of compound indexes in Mongoose?",answers:{answer:"Compound indexes in Mongoose are used to index multiple fields together, which can improve the performance of queries that involve those fields together.",fakeAnswer1:"Compound indexes are used to delete documents.",fakeAnswer2:"Compound indexes are used for creating web forms.",fakeAnswer3:"Compound indexes are used to define CSS styles."}},{id:568245790132,category:"Mongoose",topic:"Indexes and Performance",question:"How can you ensure unique values in a Mongoose schema field using an index?",answers:{answer:"You can ensure unique values in a Mongoose schema field by creating a unique index on that field using the `unique` option.",fakeAnswer1:"Uniqueness cannot be enforced using indexes in Mongoose.",fakeAnswer2:"Uniqueness is enforced using the `validate` method.",fakeAnswer3:"Uniqueness is enforced using the `delete` method."}}],Ye=class Ye{constructor(){B(this,"QuizzesData",[...Vt]);B(this,"StartQuizData",[]);B(this,"startQuiz",!1);B(this,"selectedTopics",[]);B(this,"selectedCategory","");B(this,"selectedAnswer","");B(this,"userResult",{good:0,fault:0});Tr(this,{QuizzesData:g,startQuiz:g,StartQuizData:g,selectedCategory:g,selectedTopics:g,selectedAnswer:g,userResult:g,setStartQuiz:y,setCategory:y,getAllCategories:y,setTopics:y,getAllTopics:y,getQuestionsByCategoryAndTopics:y,resetStore:y,setAnswer:y,setUserResult:y})}static getInstance(){return this.instance||(this.instance=new Ye),this.instance}setStartQuiz(){this.startQuiz=!this.startQuiz}getAllCategories(){return[...new Set(Vt.map(a=>a.category))]}setCategory(t){this.selectedCategory=t}getAllTopics(t){const a=this.QuizzesData.filter(r=>r.category===t);return[...new Set(a.map(r=>r.topic))]}setTopics(t){this.selectedTopics=[...t]}getQuestionsByCategoryAndTopics(){return this.QuizzesData.filter(t=>t.category===this.selectedCategory&&this.selectedTopics.includes(t.topic))}setStartQuizData(t){this.StartQuizData=[...t]}resetStore(){this.selectedTopics=[],this.selectedCategory="",this.selectedAnswer="",this.userResult={good:0,fault:0}}setAnswer(t){this.selectedAnswer=t}setUserResult(t){t?this.userResult.good+=1:this.userResult.fault+=1}};B(Ye,"instance",null);let lt=Ye;const lo=lt.getInstance();export{lo as Q,fo as o};
